Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Way too comfortable last night. I'm very sick
You sleeping right there you're sleeping back there Lola Lola Lola are you sleeping I see you back there you're sleeping I
See you back there. I'm sleeping. Oh
Your kitty cat. Oh your kitty cat
Hi
Get a great night. What a great night that we had last night, but we had a great guest
We have a good guest last night
It was Raven Raven taro. Thank you Raven for being here. What a great guest you were
Thank you so much. I think everybody is not a better boot. It was like
You know
Your talented reader just say, oh look I have another half a cramber
I'll drink it. I'll drink it
That's 11 30 a.m
Wow, I did have fun. It's like I so much fun. I did have fun. I
Drank too much. Maybe I drank too much guys. I
Woke up. I'm wearing a speedo
Without I wasn't wearing this last night was like, I don't know what happened
I'm shocked
Oh
So guys the speedos do they do fit perfectly our size were they
They came in this I
Don't throw me that away. I'm just keep keeping them. They fit perfectly. I love them
Have a good bye
Love what happened why I showed everything what happened? I'm covering myself
Nobody saw anything good thing
I remember I remember it's beat I made up. That's fine. That's all I do. Okay. I showed everything. Okay
Why am I I woke up? I'm wearing what are the work we get with speedos guys?
It's you know the speed is clean out there Arthur. It's great. Just I don't know for 12 hours
Super clean, I took a shower. I got
Super clean out Arthur. You'd like it. You liked it Arthur. I
Know I'm gonna bring it to you guys. There's not not clip to my
There are stains on the back of the speedo. No, no, we're not
They're not brown stain. No, they were not brown. No, we're not
I can show you right now. Let me look. I don't want you to check.
No, they're not brown. There's not there's not a check
We're not Denise kiddies. No, you're lying. We're lying
There's red white and blue they were there's not red white and brown. It's red white and blue
You're being ridiculous to these we're leaving this
You're embarrassing yourself
Hey guys also, so Alice is on band and so is Michael
That's what happened I did not I did not I didn't do that. Did I what happened though? They're not thought underwear
Did I do what guys I did not do that on my show
Hi Sean oh gosh guys, please my ass ate the speed. Oh my god. I was not
What was the day I did I did it?
I don't know what I that wasn't me guy. There was somebody on my I think somebody came on my account when I wasn't watching
Insane person. I wouldn't do these things
Redway and blue balls
My god
As everybody they come everybody saw and not never everybody was not there, please
You see something that nobody nobody was nobody saw it was like one of those streams nobody it was like five people
Everyone saw
Then in 4th of july it why why do it June 11th?
This way to as boost it all their month is supposed to go by
I'm sorry drinking
Hard to eliminate Cranberry. Yeah
But as long as they don't have a laugh that is well at least laughed
At least as long as as long as people smile, I don't care
Not embarrassed
It was very HTML it was very patriotic what I did
Natural OJ day OJ Simpson day or what?
Are they orange juice or OJ? It's not much of screenshots on
X2 X today. Oh my god
Please don't see no time. Please don't don't say that there was not screenshots was there
What happened guys what happened I was just right I was always trying to do I think oh, I'll make be the smile
Well, why did I wake up at a speedo?
Let's say you heard about the speedo incidents Denise
Guys didn't leave they look good is that x trace the x is the tracy x. Oh, no you can bet there is
Guys, how do you, how do you, how do you look?
Guys, if you all say the Pledge of Allegiance, as long as you say the Pledge of Allegiance,
I'm happy, I'm happy to represent America. I don't know what happened. I'm going to,
I mean, oh, Twitter is on Twitter. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yes
Get a cape, I'm wearing one right now. I'm wearing a cape. I can be a gay superhero
I need a lucian door. I have one right here. Where's my lucian? I have my lucian door
I'm afraid to get up right now. You're gonna see everything again. I have a lucian door mask. Hold on
Hold on guys
I
Know there's a oh here it is
Guys is this a new character new character unlocked guys home
Okay page page what happened? I did they do something weird life. I didn't do anything weird today
I
Everyone's telling me I didn't do anything
You hear me, okay. I see it. Hi CB
You said I would walk to Starbucks my speed over coffee
Maybe if you I don't want to I got you guys have a walk home
If I walk to Starbucks in my speedo, I will get arrested. I literally have to walk by the police station
Guys, let me get arrested in a speedo. I'll be embarrassing. I
Did something funny. Oh, no
Everything I clipped
Easy is easy here easy, what did you buy? Why'd you buy me these?
They've given me a superpower. I was too drunk to ride my bike. Yeah, I was
So too drunk require your lapping so hard if you get
My job is complete
You saw no you did not smell you did not see these side balls. No, they're I don't think it's horn. No, there's not. I
would know
Don't see anything
They're covered you need mom no no Doug
But did you see anything?
No, you're not going to do it you're demanding mod
Doug
Any a 12 hour cuddle session with you I have a cute little lady, but
What it's very masculine it's very
Samantha is there. I'm sorry guys. I'm sorry. I drank too much. I
Don't know how to drink so much white water alcohol side balls
I've no choice but to give me mod you full tear card is said so I don't remember that dog
So I don't tell what card is it?
There's no side balls
Don't wait it the speed of they have a large foam cup. It made me look so much better
Oh
Okay guys
If you if I made you guys smile my whole point
Existence is
Validated
People if you're not mod who gets to kick my door. Oh Doug
No, Doug, aren't you black? Doug is black
Not gonna kick anybody out of the chat. I
You kick out of Midori. I'll be the first you kick out. It's my chat
Can't come up. You can't keep yourself together. You're laughing thinking about it. Oh my god
Yeah, smelly smelly 51% of I think people do over center women so
Doug yeah
Doug what you're one month old. Hey Chrissy. What do you think J-dog J-dog? Were you impressed?
I saw myself on camera.
I thought it looked pretty good.
I was like, wow.
Christine, you're explaining this account is new
because you're either,
I know Christine, he's literally on five accounts.
He doesn't look like Paulie D either.
He's like 500 pound black guy.
I've seen this in real pictures.
Doug can you make me can you make me a new account? I'm not allowed to make a new account the new accounts
You like that you like the American on a speedo. I
Mean, I'm so wearing I'm so wearing I woke up in them. I was like what happened and then I'm not show I'm not showing
I'm not I am
Yeah
You know you look like a breath of fresh air I
Didn't know they would spit they fit perfectly
This fit perfectly
Wow
I'm gonna look back on this stream. I'm gonna be like wow. I was I was with you guys. Oh
Oh
Christine no, that's not true, but Christine
Christina's I'm sure I seen as Hispanic
Irby page Christine J dog
Yeah, I just you salute the flag. I
I want to do is inspire some American patriotism
Christine didn't see oh
Christine you have to let me know Chris. I'll show Christine
Alright easy easy. What'd you think easy? You impressed as impressive or not?
I
Should go to the protest. I want to go to them wearing these if you guys want to guys want to send me
You buzz I'll take it uber over there
That's all we're gonna sign
I'll go there. Oh, yeah, it's a miracle in a spirit J dog not everyone has to do it. I want to see J dog
I want to see I want to see everyone everyone a bikini or a speedo. This isn't guys. This is this is the new the new world
Guys you did you see me out? You see me at last night or to see another channel guys beta and I have made up
You know the beat and I made up
Did I do is that my trend center guys? I'm starting the speedo trend. I'm bringing the speedo back
It looks good. I mean it's
So well cut you thought I got the boot. Yeah. Oh
Doug no, that's not true Doug no
Easy every everybody thinks everybody likes it easy
Everybody
Then not one person that was like no no no no no not one person didn't like it everyone liked it
Oh, excuse me
Doug Christine's watching you
Like a timed out Doug I
Need a speed with a rooster
On it
There was a one like that let me see if there's one Christine is there is there a rooster speed or do you think let's let's guess
I'm gonna look it up sure there's a fire rooster underwear
It's hot damn. Oh my gosh guys. Oh
There's new photos of me
My new modeling photos are in
Hold on my new modeling photos
Yeah, I'm so handsome. Yeah
That was about on the beach
I was on a I was on a I went on a cruise ship. Let's say that's that day. Oh, oh my gosh. Oh good
Yeah, look I look great I look great
Cute I went to a floor shop and I did a modeling shoot Wow look at that. I'm so handsome guys
There's a gym modeling shoot there
Yeah, yeah
I was wearing a blue outfit. It says comfy college. I wore that in college. I
Have muscles too
My family dinner there, so they have my dress
My in a casual shirt here doing a modeling shoot I
See I was on I went to a roof in New York right there. It's what I was it. That was it. I
Look great
They're real photos
Well, Doug is Doug is a weirdo Doug Doug. What are you doing? Are you causing problems my chef?
We're my pants. Why am I not wearing pants? I'm sure I have another half a cigar in here. Hold on a second
Check the pockets. Hey, hey guys, look what I found. I found a cigar. Oh
I called
I called scribbles last night to use argue with his wife. They were arguing
Big Matt, and I called I called it
It's like I saw the phone he hung up on me
And he's like, is there someone still here?
He hung up on me.
But I was on him for like 10 minutes.
I was sitting there on him.
I was like, why is he hanging up on me?
Arguing with his wife.
He's like, you motherfucker, you're a faggot.
You're on the day of your husband.
Ah!
I love you scribbles. It was funny. It was funny. And then they both tell Steve in the same bed.
They were like, I hate you mother. And then they tell Steve, I'll hug you in bed.
It's fun. Guys, guys, guys, there's never going to be a dull moment with me, okay?
Yeah, blessings on blessings
The link okay got you I got you
That's what anyone gonna come up. Good morning guys
I found it's a half a cigar. So I'm okay
You'll find it's tear nature file
Adored led labored breath from your 450 pound body
This idea it was my pot it was just in my pocket. It's not half smoked. It's like yeah, that's what yeah
I walk to the, I think I walked to the store or something.
I must have.
Guys remind me, who got clapped last night?
Somebody got clapped, just remind me
so I don't flip them all on accidentally.
I have to check my cash out, what happens?
They're gonna be clapped, I think Michael's free
and Alice are free.
Let me hear you sing a song.
I know Seymour's the greatest, but I'm dating a semi-status.
So I've got a black eye and my arms are cast.
I know Seymour's the cutie.
Well, if not, he's got little beauty.
And we can be together, alas, a matchbox of our own.
House upon a hill, I look like Betty Crocker.
And I look like Donna Reed.
What's that and a dryer?
To keep things neat and clean There's plastic on the furniture
Ooh, somewhere that's green We make our TV dinners in our bed time
On a big, enormous, twelve-inch screen, y'all.
I miss wife, his father, he knows best.
The kids play, howdy-doody, as the sun sets in the west.
A picture from better homes and garden's magazine.
Far from Skid Row.
Someday we'll go somewhere that's green.
The big ones you're still in trouble. I supposed to talk to people like like you do. You're very insulting
You're harmless person
This was a chill, but it's a chill. I'm trying to chill
But I had a box you have to teach me
Yeah, Daniel don't you had to wrestle it you can
I'm just trying to chill something so jelly jelly. Don't be so jelly
I'm so evil. God, how am I so evil? Good morning. 27 people in chat. Awesome. I'm going to finish. Oh shit. I'm going to finish this horror limited.
Guys if Logan Paul can wear American flags be the speedo I can
Because you just have to get me to a
Billion dollars like him
Your prison
Be your prison what your prison or your prison package
That pocket your prison pocket. I
Got my hand and my pocket
And the other one, okay, just take a breath.
They put it in the purse, yeah.
J-Dog, what'd you put in there?
What, J-Dog?
How many cell phones?
I just don't know.
I wonder how many cell phones J-Dog fit up there.
Gonna wipe down the cell phone real good.
This is your appropriately good cell phone.
Perfectly it works perfectly well
Daniel, you know it I got one hand in
Did I pop it in the other ones?
handing a taxi cab
And I'll goes
Okay, I'll do a fish taco it is Wednesday. I have a couple days left. Oh
My gosh
All I had I had a piece of cheese
There's Brooks on
You're a bitch. I'm a bitch. I'm a lover. I'm a child. I'm a mother
I'm a sinner. I'm a saint. I do not feel a sin
I'm your hell
I'm not that in between you know, you wouldn't have it any other way. Oh my gosh
Hate the world today
Remember that song I wrote this song
Easy you're there. How are well come on guys
Guys as no one no one no one's convinced me to show my speedo again, so I'm not to get ready to put my clothes
On drugs alcohol
It's having the rest of the alcohol having this worth of alcohol beverage
Hey, who's there? Who's there?
Trace is sleeping. Is Lola back there? Lola, are you back there? Lola!
Do I see you? What are you doing? Did you see me in the speedo? Oh, you did?
You happy? Just Lola. Oh, you're happy. Can I show you? I'll show you.
Lola, oh Lola, come on. Let me show you. There you go. Oh
Okay, you're like, oh, hey
But my gosh, those are falling off guys. Sorry
Guys with everyone laughing as long as everyone laughs oh
Morris no, no threatening. Come on Morris. Come on. You know, it's a Jada
Yeah, Jada, and I are gonna we're gonna we're gonna be in a sauna someday nude
This is where it's not gonna be weird. It's just gonna be hey, we're just in a sauna
We're gonna look at brub baths
You know that we're gonna go to the Japanese or Chinese or whatever whatever
We go to some
Some kind of par parlor
Those are I hey, what's up Eden? Oh
My gosh, no guys don't argue. There's supposed to be United
Speedos was probably supposed to bring everyone together
Now they're brilliant
I'm like a bird. I don't need to fly away. I don't know where my soul is
I don't know where my home is, but baby, I love what beat it. No, I'm like a bird. I need to fly away
Hate the world today
And it sounds just like like I'm gonna sound like Meredith Brooks
And it's like that she copied that and then she copied that from a lot of s'mores that right guys my writer along I heard like
A lot of s'mores that and then it's a Meredith Brooks at the same time and then Natalie and Bruglia. Oh
It's an infertile of shit on
What's Natalie and Bruglia? What's the song called? I think many for Todd?
Let me find out what's called. What's the song?
Nelly for title copy Natalie and Bruglia
It's world is insane. Let me see what's called
It's called, let's see.
Nothing's right, I'm torn, I'm a lot of faith.
This is how I feel, I'm cold and I am chained,
lying naked on the floor.
Illusions never change into something real,
I'm wide awake and I can see the perfect star is torn.
You're already late.
I'm already torn.
All right.
It's like the same song.
What are you doing?
You're just sitting there licking yourself?
What?
What are you doing?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Lola, come here.
What are you doing?
Lola we see you Lola come over here Lola
No, she's not you're ignoring me Lola. I'll call your name Lola Lola
Guys this is how good cat look at her ears are not even perking up Lola Lola
You're you're you're Lola Lola
You come here. Oh, there you go
Knock knock knocking on J-Doc's door. Oh shit
Knock knock knocking on J-Doc's door
And what got it
My clipped guys guys my balls weren't show I got I was very careful to conceal my balls. I was very careful
Did you see you didn't see anything jail? Did you what there? Do you look away? Everyone's like cardigans?
How's the cardigans go?
How does it go
love me love me say that you love me fool me fool me go on and fool me love me
love me pretend that you love me squeeze me squeeze me just say that you
need me so I cry and I bet you guys you're talking to a 90s 90s baby I was
80s baby but I know the song
dear I feel we're facing a problem you love me no longer I know and maybe
there's just something that I can do to make you blue mama told me I shouldn't
bother that I ought to stick to another man
A man who surely deserves me, but I think you do.
Can't believe I drank so much like I like I had like a six pack of like the
Orange blurs and I was like 11. I was like, oh, no, it's so early now. It's 12 hours later. Hey
Time you want you want to see it, I'll show it and I'm still wearing it
I'm just wearing a blanket where my super pier okay, I'll show it again though. I have to drink the rest of the beer probably
Time you do you want to see it? It's the yes, and I have to I just check to make sure my balls are covered
Oh Daniel Daniel don't be don't be do me disgusting
Give it so if somebody sends a don't know I'll otherwise I'm putting my pants on my shirt on
Time was to see it. I'll show it
Time I'm already clipped I
Made it but floss. I mean, I did everything. I was I was almost completely naked last night
Without showing too much
While showing everything. Hey, you're kissing me you kiss me
Me to say I just thought I'm just not shy
It's not shy anymore
Hey, hey
Cut my lock into pieces this is my last resort
Sacrification no breathing. Don't fuck if I cut my own bleeding
Would it be wrong? Would it be right?
But it went like tonight. This is all that I might
I have another one to sing that song, there's TOS.
Yeah, everyone loves it.
Guys, everyone's getting patriotic.
Guys, isn't everyone getting patriotic?
That's a perfect idea.
What are you doing?
You're coming up?
Hey, one person likes to speedo, it's Lola.
Lola, you like to speedo?
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh.
Oh look.
There you go.
I'm not showing anything, I'm not showing anything.
Both of course Taylor is that who's gonna slipknot? What you doing in there?
J-Dog should get a speedo, but Mexican flag you two can stream in them. I want you J-Dog. Are you down?
Secosocial has this on go
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, not where you're down there
You're too close to my package to be growling.
Okay, how does it go?
I push my finger too much.
Ah, it's the only thing that slowly stops the ache,
but it's made of things that I have to take.
Jesus, it never ends.
It works its way inside if the pain goes on.
I push my finger too much.
Ah, it's the only thing that slowly stops.
Hey, you know that song?
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to get it closer.
I pushed my finger.
Ah.
It's a good lyric, though.
All I've got,
all I've got is insane.
You like that?
J-Doc, did you send a piece into my house
the other day, J-Doc?
Was that you?
Mexican pizza lady was extremely confused.
I said, señor, and I'm almost losing it, though.
I said, señor.
Free pizza guys like no, no, no, there's it was it was a prank. Oh
Okay, senior ideals remember that you remember that Lola and you wanted a pizza to they wasn't paid for
I'm not gonna buy a pizza without paid for
When I send me pizza guys just pay for it and they'll leave it outside
They'll eat it on screen. Otherwise, I'll just I won't answer the door
You never said anything, okay, I'll leave you to it
I'll believe you
It was El Franco
I push my finger into my it's the only thing
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
You know what you know what Sherlock Holmes
Smoked in this pipe
You're smoking cocaine in his pipe Sherlock Holmes was look it up
It was legal at the time or something. I don't know I hear a noise. Oh, hello
Rudy
But of course I'm out of tobacco, but I have to go I'm about to put on pants again
How are you wines? I found guilty. Oh, no, what are you wines? I do?
There's opium. Let me see. Hold on. Let me check
I remember there's a truly pursuit maybe smoke. Okay, too. Let me sure sure like Holmes
I think it was addicted to Holmes
Hey
Rudy, are you there? Her name it says
In Sir Arthur Coyne Dorel's Sherlock Holmes stories,
Holmes is depicted as an occasional user of cocaine.
Hold on, where did we go, Holmes?
It says, he is known to inject a 7% solution of cocaine
to stimulate his mind and enhance his powers of observation.
This habit was often criticized by his companion,
Dr. Watson, who views it as a vice
and undermines Holmes' health and judgment.
Isn't that interesting?
So it was, I was right.
J-Dog, are you coming over right away?
I want some ice cream.
Time is good.
I don't know. I can look up if he was doing heroin.
The game is afoot. Let me see.
I mean, he was doing cocaine.
Oh, he was using it. Arthur Conan Doyle says he was using cocaine and says he also occasionally
used morphine. The drug is presented as a way for homes to escape the dull root of existence
but not engaged in stimulating cases. It was important to note that both cocaine and morphine
were legal in 19th century England, though attitudes towards their use evolved through
While homes primarily use cocaine and morphine there are references to opium in the stories
The man with the twisted lip bones is depicted in an opium den while undercover, but he insists he is not indulging in the drug
Okay
Oh, I can't finish that. Oh, yeah, I finished that. Oh
Oh
Tasting the dragon
You got me, okay, let's do a J-Doc
Let's go ice cream. I need some ice cream
Let's see so
Well, I have another cigar. I found one. Oh, it has like a tiny little bit of tobacco in it
I found a little bit of tobacco then I have to walk to the store, but
Not at my speed up. That's what I'm pants
I'll be arrested
I
Got
I just want to say thank you. They're not illegal. No, they're totally legal. I haven't shipped. I wore them. I'm still
freeze the bird
literally
But these these beauties you have a little pet patting don't feel like it's this sister's I
Don't feel like dancing
I listen this is just
And I don't feel like dancing how I did that. It's another song it goes
Any which way any which way they also know another way when invisible lights
Move through your eyes, you know, I know sisters. They're good
Look up invisible lights
Daniel I know music. I'm a good music. I'm gonna music person
I don't feel like dancing.
I don't remember exactly, but I remember.
How about this one? What's the song?
What's the song? Hold on.
Is it called Captain or something? Let me tell you what it's called.
It's a really good song. Scissors, scissors.
Let's see.
Look up the song. Let's see. This is just Laura. I don't know. I can't find the other one.
I'm fun guys all about having fun. I'm about to come pants and go to the store. I'm a tobacco now
Okay, I'm a tobacco, okay
Whoo, what day is it sirs? It's Wednesday. It's only Wednesday. Wednesday, June 11. I
I sent a picture, a really cute picture, I'll send it to you on your birthday.
Happy birthday.
Cute, huh?
Do I have more pictures?
I don't know.
Okay.
We love, we love, uh, Betty White.
That's like her grandma.
Okay, that's what, that's what grandma right there.
Hey, hey, Rudy, I see you. Rudy came out.
Rudy.
Betty White.
Shake it, shake it.
Shake it like a Polaroid picture.
I'm sorry guys. I'm feeling so silly today.
Shake it, shake it. Come on, shake it like a polaroid picture.
Hold on. My god, what are you at the beach?
You have me already? Hold on, I have to check this out. I'm gonna pin my link too.
Can I see Vanessa? Yeah, I can.
I need lyrics though
Michael everybody everybody pays like me $20,000
Michael do you see me in this in my speedos?
Do you want to see
You didn't pay heads. You want to see?
Michael Michael they're American flags veto. They're so good. Oh, no, you see Michael tell me you're gonna look at the screen
Is it murder there?
She may be but no
There's more I want to see I mean American flag Speedo emerge from my pants on so if your last chance
Go ahead Michael
Michael once might you want to see Michael just tell me yes you want to see oh, I know I don't want to see it Michael
Just say just say Michael just say yes
No, yes the word yes, I'll say you know
This is a safety safety senior
No, sir, you're the poor for board
Hospitals
No, I'm gonna show I'm gonna show you Michael Michael. I'm gonna show you
Yes
The poor for more Michael's is for poor for war
Oh, so that means show me your speed, okay? No, you see? No, no, no, no
Michael you asked to see Michael you're looking
Okay, Michael just look one time just look one time. Okay never mind never mind
What you said I just did like I like rating them
the
are you off
well I'm not looking at it though so I don't even know
but you glanced I said you glanced I was on there for like a minute
you looked at screen once you saw
did you see or no
no well I was blind for a minute
you were blind
are you sure
you want to see one more time
no
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you
I know I look good in that. I look good. I know I look good.
My girlfriend says that you're a very good looking man, but you're not very attractive.
Does that make any sense?
No, it does not.
Myrna, F-F-E-U.
Don't say that.
Myrna, you're in trouble.
Myrna, stop it.
I don't believe she said that. I don't believe she said that she wouldn't say such a beautiful thing
But you're not you're not as
Babe
Let me talk to me right if she ran out of the house because she was like oh stop the words look
She likes she likes it
You're being you're being naive, you know that right?
Michael if I option off my speedos on a wash not wash
How much did you pay for them?
Nothing
Are you okay? Are you okay? You want my speedos?
Listen, are you okay? No, I'm not
what
you know you have sent me
I may have upset you
you have upset me
you have upset me now
ow
because you didn't you wouldn't look at me messing around
I was trying to get
why would I look at you with your speedos
come on
I'm so cute though I'm so cute
you don't like it
I don't know because I haven't seen it
so I don't know
I'm trying to show you I don't want to look at it. Yeah, but you said you said you said you said you said you can't judge
Do you see that?
Michael, but I don't psyche so you want to see Michael you want to see I see say yeah, they see they see
Like psych stop Michael
They pull her for I'm gonna tell beat on you. Yeah, it's okay
Don't do it
Do it Michael do it. Don't do it Michael
Saki
Michael
Doing it do it. Don't do it
Michael what what do you want? What do you want to get a screen just look at the screen?
No, I don't want to look at it. Let's look at it one time. It's one time. Oh, I don't I don't look at it
Guys that now I'm embarrassed now. Oh my god
Hey, I'll tell you this I guarantee you you like that tattoo. That's how you dress. It's you
It's right above your heart. So
You literally took a shit of
Burn Diamond stream and they tell
it talking about wearing a spew
like I'll say you're you're banned
you're banned. Oh shit.
Sticks on here.
Yeah.
It was all.
Don't kick sick.
Come on.
I mean, I like sick.
I wouldn't say I love him.
You're attractive.
There's an attraction there.
What for for sick sick? Yeah. Yeah. No, no, of course not
Okay, well, I'm sorry say I tried cuz you're really cute Michael. You know, you're really cute. You know, you're really cute
Sucking my Michael
Michael Michael Michael if you could Michael if you could see me now here on a fun ship cruise
We're eating fancy food and doing what we choose
I don't know. I don't know.
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
You love me as a lover? You say you love me as a lover?
No, you're being very disrespectful. No, I'm not. No, I was not using her actual
I was trying to be respectful and he's the alias shut up. Takey shut up
Just shut up. Okay
Just be quiet, please
I'm actually very nicely like I'm actually being very polite to you can just shut the fuck up
I know but I know I Michael I like Marianne. I like Marianne. Okay. I like
I want to use your mic. I'm gonna use a real name on my show Michael trying to use aliases. I'm not I'm being very very careful. I
Love I love Marianne. She's awesome. She's awesome
Yeah
It's not okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry Michael Michael. You know, I was on Benny's it at night. You know it to Benny's
I was on your channel and you fucking passed out last night. So what does it pass out?
No, it was the night before last and I went to Benny's and then he let me on the panel and
Talked to him and now we're friends again
No, I'm on blog I'm on block. I take the last hour on blocks. He unblocks me. He likes me
You know, he he blocked the guy blade. I told everything that blade did
I have a doubt that he'd like to
for the soul.
He let me on his show for half
hour.
He said he loves me and he
unblocked me on all my accounts.
So he didn't like me?
No, he doesn't.
He doesn't.
So he's spending an hour of his
day talking to me, smiling.
He had a shirt off last night.
He's working out.
He looks really good.
Have you seen him?
to say he doesn't like you like that
you're a liar, well
Psychic remember what you did lie all the time. What do you like? I'm not like you for you
You're in P remember the pink boxers and I was like how much he got the pink boxers, and then you were naked in the next
10 seconds or that that bullshit you're lying
I'm not lying. I'm not lying Michael show me everything Michael show me everything
No, that's not true
But guys Michael Michael said Michael said Michael said
Michael said send me $10. I'll show you my butthole and I did and then he said oh
He said that was my brother on the phone. Oh, I can't I can't do it. That's that was what Michael did
Okay, so Michael is the origin of the butthole scan guys. That's not true. You do that Michael. Yes, you did
Psyche take it back remember. No, no, no, no, remember
So I go love you brother. I love you as a friend
But you need to take that shit back because you're fucking absolutely lying right now
Michael you do you have a pair of pink boxes or not? You know, you have a pair of pink boxers or not
What they're pure pair of pink boxers, right?
I don't know fucking pink boxes. We don't know
Yeah, they are
And they have the tip of the tip of the tip of the pig on them, right michael, you remember
Can you dance for me?
Hello
Listen listen listen, can you chill the fuck out? No, how much do we drink? How much do we drink today?
Half of
Honestly question, how much are we doing today?
Not as much as a boy to drink as I have another twisted tea right now. It's only noon
See our bandolay believes me a smelly believes me
God he believes me
Michael do you remember you gave me a lap dance at one time fuck Goddy first of all hold up number one fuck Goddy and then number two
You need to respect your elders. Okay, cuz you should be
Come on now. Oh my elders. You're 47 years old. Are you talking to me? I'm 36
You should respect your elders man. Come on now
But you're you're not you're I'm your elder you're supposed to respect me
Well, I do respect you. That's what I'm saying. You're 40 something and I'm 36
No, but you say you told me that you told me not to show my speed. He said don't show me speedo
Don't you don't want to see it? How's that respectful? I'm very offended
Michael put me put me Michael put Mary Anne on the phone put Mary Anne on the phone
Her name's not Mary Anna. Her name's Mary. No
the
you don't know any more
I don't
know
her name is Maryanne
give sucky twenty-five dollars
kick me off
there you go
hi prairie
yeah our bandley loves spiky scenes
spiky spiky spiky
Paige come up here please
do it Paige
Come up here, please, baby. Come on, baby. Don't come page. Don't call me baby
What's that song go? Because I'm like
my dog
He's being an asshole. So hey, I'm fine. Hey, I'm fine. I he asked to see me in the speedo
I showed him and then he pretended like he's around
No, please you beg you beg me to show you you're like, are you what you said? I want to see it
You're ready to do it. You did the pledge you did the pledge of allegiance. I saw you do the pledge of allegiance that my bow
No, it's not true. You did it. Okay. He has he has to go to the store, so
Well, she has to go to start man. I want to I want to shame
J-dog is projecting his bisexuality. Please don't feed into it if I feel safe. No art art
Happens between you and J-dog happens between you and J-dog I'd lick the screen. Okay. Oh God, I did not I did not
No, and our generally just don't report it. It's don't report this is you always just blocked a dog
You don't have to do anything else
Doesn't work anyway. I'm YouTube loves me. You do fucking love me. You did they do you love me?
Just look
Who makes a screen about you
Guys a bitch anyways, so it's all good. No, no, no, no, no Gotti go home first of all God
He's God. He's in the mafia first of all. So first of all, you don't want it
Yeah, I'm gonna be honest with you man. You're a fucking you're a fucking bitch for anybody that fucking anybody
It seems for you. No, it's all good
He doesn't he doesn't he's sweet sweet threatens my life on every day. That's why I'm terrified of Gotti
You know, so you're scared of Gotti. Wow. I'm not scared of Gotti. Michael. He's in him. He's in the mafia
He knows made made men the mafia
Yes
You don't hear his voice you didn't hear in his voice
He sounds like everybody ever does the pranos before
I don't give a fuck
I really don't give a fuck
Gotti's not a fucking
You know what Goddy is Goddy is a fucking bitch. He's a bitch-ass nigger. That doesn't even know what
You know what then go suck his dick go suck his dick sucky go do it
He hasn't asked me to so I'm not going to go suck his well then he doesn't have to you know why because he doesn't
Fackin have to fucking ask for shit. You know why cuz Goddy is a bitch
Should I got a guy you gotta come up here guy. Hey, do you ever see the movie Goodfellas Michael?
You know, you know, Gotti isn't that isn't that a movie you ever heard of the movie Scarface?
Fuck you. Yeah him
He's in that movie too
No, he's not yeah
He plays out between his brother. He plays out between his younger brother. Jay dog Jay dog come up here, bro
Come come come defend your brother man. Come on now. Let's go
And also the same time y'all can fuck each other, you know, I mean so fuck you fuck sucky fuck
Fuck time
I don't know why you put it on my business up there. I'm trying to take a shit here
I don't take a shit in peace. I guess I'll fucking pee for once
It's the only time I get some fucking quiet
I'm trying to take a fucking
You want a lust over stikie
Ron let's do this
What the fuck do you want
I don't want anything from you on the fucking phone
How much you want to bet that I want
25 bucks 25 bucks get her on the fucking phone
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Oh, well, I'll tell you sorry to Paige. Paige, I'm sorry. I love you, though.
We're not friends today. We're not friends today. You're so desperate, everybody.
He's so desperate for love.
Shut the fuck up, baby.
Thank you. Give him the love that he needs. Take him in.
Send him your speedo.
I love you. Shut up, bitch.
Send your shit to Michael, let him wear it. Let him think of you. I love you, baby.
no, but I will, I'll wear whatever Paige tells me to
I want you to wear an apology to everybody who just insulted
I apologize to everybody except for fucking, um
G.O.D.
Well, those were my homies, so fuck you then.
Michael, are you still on the page?
First of all, what is the page?
I am absolutely on the page.
Michael, the only reason you're here is because Psyche is attracted to you.
That's the only fucking reason.
Well, I mean sucky's been
And you're attracted to him just admit it I'm attracted to him
It's clear fucking day everybody can see it
Are you done hey, oh, I agree with God, I agree with God, you know, it's getting fucking denied, right?
No, is he done?
No, I'm just gonna figure out if he's done.
Hey, fuck you guys, we're coming to the store with me now.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
What's the story?
Um, I gotta go get, um, I think it's gotta be this.
Hey, shut the fuck up, let me see.
Cheese and crackers.
Look how he talks to the women on the panel.
You're totally gay.
Totally fucking gay, this guy.
No doubt in my mind.
Gotta be.
Fuck.
You can do better
Hey, what do we get wine and cheese?
Yeah, we're gonna go get some wine and cheese for Michael
Well
Why are you bringing up her name is I can
Who's your name?
Myrna's at work right now.
Myrna's working hard right now so the scrub can stay at home and do this.
Myrna.
What's so fucking ridiculous?
Gosh.
You can do better.
Myrna.
That's enough.
That's awesome.
Awesome.
He thinks he's worth $25.
Yeah, I got worked out. Shut up.
You know what?
Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you.
You're priceless. Hey, you're priceless.
What did you say? What did you say?
What did you just say to me, Michael?
What did you say to me?
I just told you. I said,
fuck your fucking stupid ass,
fucking Beatles, Keely,
on your fucking chest.
You stupid ass.
Hey, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he's stupid, he
Fuck all y'all. You know what I'm saying?
What? What are you saying?
What are you fucking saying?
Do you know what I'm saying, bitch?
Did he just say fuck God? Did he just say that?
Shut up, Michael.
Did he fucking say that? Did I hear him right?
No, Michael.
You just fucking cursed yourself, pal.
Why are you fucking cursing?
Shut your mouth, everybody.
Shut your mouth, anyways.
Don't ever tell me what to do.
Well, what I'm gonna do and I'm gonna do it
Page page obviously left for a reason fucking coward shut the fuck up
page
She left her
Go pay $25 you sucky $25 and then pay an example. I don't give a fuck
care
I can care less
And then the fucking
Jish over here is a fucking piece of ass coward
Shut up
Now a gish
You know what I'm talking about and also at the same time psyche's a bitch, too
Yeah, you hear me what did you say? Will you call me something?
You're a bitch, too. You're a bitch. Why?
Because you are a bitch
It's all coming out guys
Michael do you want to see my speed up?
No, I don't see shit of you. You want to see it say yes. You're you're a fucking asshole. No, fuck you
See the thing is you don't want to defend anybody except
I
Fuck you. Fuck you
Man, why are you mad?
So I keep fucking
You know what go be on go be on beat us channel. How about that?
Which has happened which is that Michael Lee
Michael
Michael I can't hear you anymore Michael
Hi, sweet pea. I don't know. I don't know
Michael's what he went nuts
I want to see you everyone saying one. That's just Daniel
You she said that you see other people. He's not very nice. No, I mean I was I was so nice
Asked to speak to Marianne. I was like, yeah, no
Sweet pea. I don't know. I'm feeling a little bit naked right now
What are you people in the chat
Yeah, but so they're so angry
Michael I was I was so I was kind
Michael try to find someone that's been as kind to you as I have even though it's joking around
You're gonna grill burgers. I need one Oliver. You cook one up for me
Sweet pea, I'm sorry. I don't know why
Hi, sweet pea. I
Don't know why
Tell me why
Ain't nothing but a heartache. Tell me why
I want it that way
Not fish burgers again, I don't want to eat them. I only eat fish tacos
I don't I can't digest any other you know kind of food. Hey Daniel
Okay, I'm gonna put my pants. Yeah, I'm putting on the pants. Okay
putting on my pants
You're not gonna see this Beatles
Someone wants to donate they can't I'll show them
But I'm gonna need to cold right now. I'm gonna throw my pants. Oh my gosh
You look
Oh
Nobody saw anything
I'm a skeleton
Casey stop it. I'm a skeleton
My guys my father my father was skeletor yes, I'm not embarrassed
Jack Skellington beats
Oliver, no doxing. No doxing.
My tree
Everyone clip it
That picture the branches
They're called my armpits. Okay, not all brands on my armpits
Slender man. Yes, so yes
Don't call me my improper name in public
Hey tricks you come over here tricks don't say hi tricks
One tricks one. Let's say hi. Come on
Let's say hi
Hi
Hi, I'm mr. Tricks. I'm mr. Trixie
This is a lava lava
Oh
Your sweetheart, huh your sweetheart you can't oh
Hi, okay, they pet you lick me you look up my sense really stop licking up my sense you love how it's
You're licking my sense
What here you have a kiss hi mr. Oh
Hello
Hello, sir
Yes, thank you, yes, thank you
This bank
Oh, I spanked you I spanked you. Oh, oh, you love it. You love me. Oh, you love me
Oh, you're so sweet hearted cat. You're a sweet hearted cat. Oh, you're a sweet hearted cat, huh?
Tell me why
Oh
Good yes
Ain't nothin' but a heartache, tell me why I want it that way.
What, you like it?
Tell me why ain't nothin' but a trick, see Tell me why I never want to hear Tricks sing
I want it that way You are my fire, my one desire
When you hear people say
Well, it tricks his way
Tell me why ain't nothing but a heartache
Tell me why I
Never want to hear it Rick say
Well it that way
Oh, you like it? You like it?
Chase.
There you go. You're happy?
What do you hear? What do you hear?
Chase, what do you... Wait, wait, what's wrong?
Tell me why?
Yeah, I don't know why Michael Michael guys. I wasn't I was being nice to Michael. Well, why do you we went off on me?
Imagine it's like friends. I mean
Treats his enemies like this. Imagine how he treats his friends
Tell me why
One it tricks his way
Oh, so happy you're happy cat, huh?
So look at the camera, look at the camera, look at the camera, look at the camera, look at the camera
Here's your noise your noise
Who's that?
I was the nor she's good. Yeah, the nor come in the house. It's probably coming out. Okay, go
Nor is good
And now he's let you on sick, I don't know about that. I don't know sick
Want to end my I don't end my stream you want to see my speedo say you do
That's it. Oh, he said it. He said he wants to see my sped up the speedo
Also, it's a I'll let you on
You found a shirt too. Where's my shirt? Oh, I find a shirt. So sorry. Oh shit
You think it'll be okay? I think you will be
Michael is no fence
Tell Marianne I said hi
Oh my gosh, I'm stuck. I'm stuck. There goes
Your band we'll say why did you get banned? What is that picture you're showing?
This is a penis
Trying to go into my what what is that? What is your profile picture? It looks like a
What is that look at gonzo?
You're Matt Michael something why are you so mad at me?
Michael I don't think you hear me. Well, I guess I like this guy. Oh you hear me. Okay. You're mad at me
Why
Cuz you're an asshole
You're not
No, hell no, I'm not I'm not asshole. I'm shit on nobody
Okay, fuck
Michael you're Michael you are an asshole you are you are
It's not bad. I'm not saying you're bad. I'm just saying you're an asshole
Got a life. What's up, buddy
What do you guys chat would you agree with her or do you disagree? I know Michael you're really cute
You're really cute. I love Mary Ann. I love you. I think you're a great couple
Goddamn
I'm not trying to use a real name Michael Michael. I'm trying to do some privacy
Fuck yeah, her name is Mary Ellen, right?
Man, you're fucked up, bro. Her name's not Mary Ellen Dumbass
But no, I don't want to give her real Michael. I'm going to say I want to keep her anonymous
Okay, no, it's not okay. Just forget it, man
Stop doxing your girlfriend Michael Michael. You know how cute you are
You didn't hear me
He's cute Michael, you know you can't hear you I can hear you but you're being a dumbass
Okay, if you ever say if you ever say psyche's cute, I'm gonna take it as an insult from now because Michael
I said Michael's cute. He's like, oh
You're insulting me no
I'm not I'm not insulting anybody. You know what? You actually I'll assault one person
I'll insult one person. It's not you second. I'm so
fucking
Goddy fucking bitch ass motherfucker
Stupid ass and then he lies and says that his girl. Well, whoa, let me take the back his fucking
girlfriend is
Tiffany and suddenly is fucking his actual sister
Fucking bitch ass motherfucker. Fuck you stupid ass bitch
Claim yourself as you are and not claim yourself as me stupid ass bitch
Fuck you stupid ass fucking faggot
And I'm not talking about you suck you
Stupid ass bitch
You ain't gonna do shit. You ain't gonna do shit on me. That's what I'm saying
Fucking faggot ass
Stupid ass bitch. You ain't gonna do shit
You ain't gonna do anything and anybody in the chat they got a problem with me
Fuck you and fuck your mom bitch. Fuck you
Stupid ass fucking fag shut the fuck up and know your role before you fucking come to me
bitch ass
Shut the fuck up
Stupid ass pussy
You ain't gonna do shit
You ain't gonna do shit and then psyche ain't gonna do shit either
You know why cuz I can't get do anything because he's on fucking
Beatles fucking channel. So he ain't gonna do shit either
So fuck you fuck all y'all y'all fuck everybody fuck you
There you go
Are you okay, Michael?
I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you
I want to I want to go visit Elisa and spend the night. It's in the night of your house and then fly back. I see one night
Okay, you're not gonna do anything. That's what I'm saying. You're not gonna do anything
No, I didn't say I was gonna say it's been in the head sleeping your yard. I'll sleep on a lawn chair. Okay
I love you to death
You're my brother, but you're not you're not you're not helping man. You're really not you're really not helping
All right, you get it sucky do you understand what I'm saying do I read it's been on no, okay, so
Pero do it as that
Then I'm with her or a
You know saying
Este...mucho...jodes
I'm what? I'm a jodes?
Te vas a enseñar en escoño, meh
O sea, estupido
Michael...
Que chido
Como estas, Miguel
Miguel, que es un problema
Yo hablo español, yo conozco que...
Tu...ah...tu hables
Que...que...fuckin' papi
¿Qué es eso? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué?
¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué?
¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué?
¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué?
¿Qué?
Muy muy muy estupido
You call me pendejo Michael?
No
Just call me a stupid hoe again Michael stop it
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Cuz you deserve it. That's what you deserve. Listen
Listen, Linda listen
You actually speak that way with beta beta actually knows the words of the sling
So she would know right
No, she wouldn't know that
She's he was just these bad and she's these Arab. She knows the Persians. So I was it right? She knows that the words, right?
See
See okay, all right, so now you want to speak Spanish even though you don't know Spanish
You're you're I'm your Miguel. Okay?
Do it's not local
Chono, I'm a spanish
But I'm a kid
It's been your spoopy to
Okay, you understand that you understand that part
He's calling me a stupid hoga. God. I'm really I'm gonna be offended about five minutes
Michael, I'm gonna call you super whore. I'll call you stupid. I didn't call you super whore
Now if you want me to say you said you said you said to us who's stupid, oh I
Said it's stupid. Oh, they're my yenta
You know what that means. I mean stupid fucking piece of shit
Michael, ¿Por qué? ¿Por qué? ¿Por qué?
¿Por qué? ¿Por qué? ¿Por qué?
¿Por qué? ¿Por qué?
¿Por qué?
Ponyo, it's that do like Michael Michael. You're so it. Yo, you're so it would money cone
Eat you know, fuck you you're a bastard bitch. Fuck you and fuck your mom and fuck your dad. I'm gonna fuck
You're gonna call you because what you just said to me is that oh, I'm a son of a bastard and my mom's a bitch
Fuck no everybody else. I said I said I said I said I said Michael's the unicorn
No, you didn't bitch
My son body code uniform
No, you didn't you didn't say that
Why are being so aggressive like fucked up because you know what in the meantime?
I was being very polite to you and now I'm being very mean to you. So
Why are we mean what I do? Why are you being mean?
What do you mean why I'm being mean?
Why?
Because I have to because you're the one that's being mean to me
And I don't I don't really give a fuck about anything that you or anybody in the chat has to say
You got it
No, it's easy Michael Michael. No one said one bad. I don't see any comment about you
Michael just explain and all of y'all all of y'all. So what did you say?
You know what I said
This I mean, I heard what you said, but the Chatham say anything
Sweep sweepy. He's a player. He needed beers. He wouldn't eat 13 times
Sir more it's five o'clock somewhere. Is that bad? I don't know. What are they saying? Is there something about you?
I don't think so. I don't give a fuck
I don't give a fuck
Shut up psyche
Remember, okay. Remember because remember you
You personally on your side about as far as it goes with
beta
you gave out yourself with beta me personally I help you out okay so you
should be very careful about who you're speaking to and who you're talking to
you know I'm saying no or yes like all I know is I'm in love with you
I know I've always been in love with you. I've always will be in love with you
I mean, I'm taking away from Mary Ann. I want you to move to California with me. Okay?
Bro you need to chill me just chill. All right
Just chill Michael. I'm in love with you Michael. I Michael. I'm in love
No, you're not
Michael you're so cute. You're you're like you're really cute
Michael I didn't have I'm about to literally call be the right now
You tell me that he's gonna be cool
Well, I'm not gonna tell be the ship because obviously I'm not fucking talented
But I guarantee you that she's gonna be on another level
And she's not gonna like believe anything that I'm saying
That you're saying you know I'm saying Michael Michael. Are you drinking Michael? Have you drinking?
Have I been drinking? Yeah
Fuck yeah
That explains why you're being so disagreeable
You're being disagreeable. You know why cuz you're fucking bitch ass coward
That's what it is
it's like you don't understand okay listen you're not understanding anything that I'm saying you're not
understanding anything that anybody is saying you know I'm saying no you don't right okay that's you
fucking coward man
and then when I when I say that I'm trying to bring my girlfriend in here you ain't gonna do shit
I'm not going to shit. I'm not going to I said I want to say hi to Mary and I didn't say
Fucking
I'm just trying to get I'm not trying to say a real name on the show. I'm
Trying to give her alias. I
Don't care I don't care
All right, you got it. I don't care
All right, you got it
You're mad at me Michael
What would it be mad at you?
Hey, you call it. I mean you call me a thousand names this morning. You didn't want to see my speedo
Tell me to go away
Michael I got this beat up for you. I got it for you. You did you did you we want to see it?
Psych psych. I love you. All right. You're my brother. All right
We all get along. All right, but the thing is when you're gonna fucking talk shit about
And I'm not talking
I just want to work out in the gym and the game they take a shower and then tell each other off
That's all I wanted to do. Okay
Yeah, it's fine. Okay. Yeah, okay. That's all I wanted to know
Okay, so I'm gonna leave you alone because I'm in love
Hey, Chumkicks, you're you're full of shit, man, bro. What?
Michael, you know how much I love you
You're full
Well, why are you saying that Michael? Do you know I did Michael?
Do you remember when we were in that we were in the shower together and I was looking I looked down remember that
You're my bro. You're such a fucking liar, bro. You remember that Michael? It was one time and you bit
You're bending over telling off your feet. I remember look you saw me looking at you
You remember that Michael Michael do you remember Michael? That's okay
It's okay Michael. No one's gonna judge you remember you bench over and I'll be touted off your feet
And I was you saw me looking at your butt you're being a bitch stop
Yeah, are you done so okay guys Michael has a big he didn't hit the big dick he does
it's, it's uncut, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's
Have to have to let you go sucky anyways. I love you sucky. I love you like as a friend
I love you okay, but I need you as a boy as a boy is a boyfriend. I
Love you as a friend a friend
Very nice. I'm a boyfriend a friend a friend benefit a friend benefits
It's like you have to let you go, man. You're you're you're being way naive right now. So
Okay, Michael Michael. I'm in love with you Michael. No, fuck you. I am
Why would I let you on my show? Why do I let me on my show so much because you're so cute
Because because I can get you $25 easily
No, I like your smile. Look at this guy
Uh, yeah, he's a good memory and he's a cute couple
No, he's cute. He's cute. You bro. Thank you. Anyways, what anyways?
Saki, I love you. You're my friend. Um, I want to be
Peace
You want to be my boyfriend?
I gotta let you go over here. I gotta
Michael Michael Michael are you back? You're back though, right?
Listen, listen, you're not helping all right because you and Benny are fucking cowards
Yeah, Benny
Yeah, you and what are you bringing Benny into this?
You know why?
Are you jealous of our relationship?
Why would I be jealous for?
To be iron love
No
We want to bring you into it. We want to bring you into this whole thing
Benny's not gonna get into it. You know why yeah, no, no, but Benny already here. He said yes
You always is you and then we're gonna we're all gonna get married
Okay
Well, you can think whatever you want. Um, also by the way, God is a fucking bitch ass
Fucking coward and his fucking sister who's not his actually sister. It's a fucking coward, too
like guys anything else Michael has some big pair of balls because
He's talking to
My god, he's literally in the mafia. I mean and Michael's talking so Michael has
Fuck out of here, you know fucking mafia. He's a fucking bitch ass coward and also he lied about
This fucking bitch being his fucking sister and shit
He ain't his sister. You know what he is. He's a fucking coward as
Mike Michael Michael, but is Mary on your sister?
No, she's my girlfriend. What the fuck? Okay, I
Thought I remember Mary Ann. What you talking about? Oh
So I was right. I was right
You're right about what her name was Mary Ann
Her name's not Mary Ann you dummy her name's not Mary Ann
Okay
I'm really confused. I'm gonna be really confused
Michael but Nicola, do you know I love you Michael? I
Love you too, man, but you're
I'm a what I love you too, but you're pain in the ass. I'm pain in the ass. Okay. It's okay. Yeah
Sure, we can hug it out. We can hug it we can hug it out. I
Mean, I'll give you a big hug, but I'm not I'm not gonna like I wouldn't say that I'm gonna hug it out with you
What if I touch here? What if we give a hug like a bear hug and then I touch your butt what what's gonna happen?
No, you probably get slapped in the fucking face and I'll fucking punch you
What if I what if I like that?
That's that's on you bro. That's on you
Okay
I'm gonna grab your butt. You can stop my face. No, that's it. It's gonna be it
All right. Well, you're about to get fucked up if you do that shit
So it's all good. What if I touch it once this I got baseball like pretty much in baseball
And you just go to home run and I just give it a slap. No, you're about to get fucked up, bro
What I said, you're about to get bug
Michael you play baseball, right
Michael on Michael
You can't hear me Michael
Think it was awesome. But guys, by the way, I did see Mike Michael. He put on the baseball pants. I
Told I first fell in love with them
But is it's a nice but
Michael do you hear me?
Michael here's a nice, but so I was in the locker room I smacked I smacked it
He he's laughed all he do is laugh. Oh
He left he left
Michael's a power bottom. He's the power is a total complete power bottom. He loves it
Michael's a level he's in love with me. I know he's in love with me
Get out Michael all Michael I'll give you a nice little back rub
Hi guys, I don't know if you'll get so upset
I mean, is that an innocent person?
Michael? Are you there? Hello Michael? He's gone.
Okay, well, it's okay. He's uncomfortable. I know.
They didn't know there's love there I kids I can feel it. I can't I know he loves me
He wouldn't be here for months on my channel. He would he wouldn't he would just like he would just have left and said
Oh, I don't like this guy. He likes me
Yeah, Mary Mary and calls him
It's okay
It's my fault. I know it's everything's my fault
Everything my fault. I'll take all the blame
aqua see foam shame
Choking on the ashes of an enemy in the sun
Sorry
Michael stop calling me up. Don't bother beta. Stop it Michael. Do not call beta
No
Hey guys
Tell me this is just my personality. I'm not trying to show I'm not trying to show
Had a little bit of troll blood and so I did it happens naturally, but I'm trying to troll. I love Michael
He is really cute. He's really cute. I don't know why he gets so upset
I'm like, oh here you're cute. Oh leave me alone leave me alone leave right near the Michael
Where's my hair hold on
I did it, oh wait, you're here, wait, wait, wait, you're here, that's okay, that's okay,
I hear this, great, does it look good now?
I brushed it.
Happy, you're happy, Cap?
I can have a kid oh oh oh oh Michael come back oh oh Michael come back don't you know you got a
hope I need I was wrong and I just can't live without you Michael come back
I can't tell Michael to do anything
Are you laughing sassy? I know I'm laughing too
Yeah, I got I woke up. I roll out of bed and I came on stream
Look, I was I was still my speed. I was still in my speedos and I showed them again a few times
Michael and I'm really insulted Michael
Michael you have to admit my butt looks pretty good Michael. It's not my butt
I saw I saw I was I'm I'm I've all I love myself. You're rounding your saw sweepy. I know
It's on it's on rewind in Michael's house. I didn't stain them sweepy. They're not stained
They're completely clean
No, he didn't get the he raised quit he raised quit
He has a booth of he just raised quit
Where's Alex 28 people in chef by the way guys rare a fun day today. I'm already I woke up drunk
He's like what he saw he did I know smell smell you
These Speedos are gonna give me places. You got a comfortable. That's okay
Guys his speed is these people are gonna hit me to the White House
They would slap me but he didn't say where yeah, he wants to slap my butt
Okay, Michael Michael it's not gay if you enjoy it
But you should see Michael's butt
We play baseball he pulls them up. He's like the pitcher or the catcher. I don't know. He's one of the two
They just fit so good on him. Oh
scrumptious
Slap me dick
Stop call guys stop calling Mary leave Marianne alone Marianne is innocent person in this situation
Mary and didn't do anything Mary Ann are you Mary and Mary Ann come on the show
Michael is that true
It's okay Michael
Gay is okay
I'm gay
Wait, what wait? Why you hey?
Michael's fine
Michael, can I smell yo dick? I want to smell it one time
It's gonna take a three-hour tour
with Michael
And Mary Ann to Mary Ann. That's your name is Mary Ann
It is building the island guys guys
Ginger and the millionaire and his wife the movie star ginger
Or what's her name the professor and Mary Mirna?
Myrna
Can I smell yo dick? I remember that song. I know that song. I remember that. Baby, can I? Yeah
That's pretty easy
I'm going to I'm gonna be I mean at least in Jordana. I'll get I'll be in the speedos in the airport
She's got if you fix me up in the airport. I'll be in speedos. I will I promise
If I don't get arrested before I do it I will
be in the airport
Waiting for her rejeep and I'll be my speedos
By the way, Alisa, thank you. Alisa was so sweet. I sent her a few messages.
I forgot. I sent her songs. I'll sing it.
Let me see the song. How does it go? It goes...
I have to wait for the lyrics. It goes...
How does it go? I have to wait.
Somewhere that's green
Hold on let me think
No, I
Send the songs I said so I send this song to Alisa and then
She said oh, don't just take this nice song. She said
She said wow, I love that song. It's saying that in my high school play
So also in the song
Somewhere that's green. It's a really good song
I'll sing it
Me do you guys want me to see it? Yes pretty diamond you want to see pretty pretty diamond you haven't seen 30
I'm gonna do a lap dance for the diamonds. Okay good. I'm gonna see
Lurdy
Okay, yeah, I know I know
You like that, okay, you know, there's no skin marks on this guy's stop being so cool. I
Look good in them. I look good in them. I know I look good. I also wouldn't do it
You like that 40 I know you like that he goes
I know Seymour's the greatest, but I'm dating a semi-statist, so I got a black eye and my arms in a cast.
Still, that Seymour's a cutie, well, if not, he's got inner beauty.
And I dream of a place where we can be together at last.
A matchbox of our own.
A fence of real pain-link.
A gorilla on the patio.
Disposal in the sink.
Water and a dryer.
M-s-s-s-s-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i
Alright, here's the thing, okay.
He weighs and trims the grass.
He loves...
Oh, can I sing my song?
No, no, no, I'm kidding.
He mow in a weed.
I look like Betty Crocker.
And I cook like Donnery.
It's fantastic on the furniture.
Oh, that's racism.
To keep it neat and clean in a pine star-scented air.
Somewhere that's green
Cowboys say hi
Can I say you said you want me to do it? Can I sing my song?
Yes, you can. Are the music my speedo yet?
I'm good brother. Thank you
Okay, I'll show you once again. No, no, no, it's good. You're good. You're good. You're good. You're good
No
Other why are you screaming?
Dude, I don't have to see that dude
Everyone wanted to see everyone wanted to see every literally everybody in the chat was said yes. Look sweet. He said yes
See
Arthur do you see the back?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Now I'm insulted. I've just insulted this.
Dude, what the fuck is wrong with you, dude?
Well, Arthur, someone's that made a speedo, I'm gonna show it off.
I look good in it.
Alright, so if I send you a 9mm, are you gonna put it through yourself?
If it's a 9mm speedo.
Hey, what the fuck is wrong with you? Are you smoking something? Nobody wants to see that shit
Everybody literally everybody in the chat is saying they wanted to see it. They're really everybody
true
repeat smelly
reality Nancy
Every everybody said yes for a diamond even for them one to see it
Anyways, can we talk about the
The cat and I mean the elephant in the room
What is the elephant? Tell tricks tricks wants to know
Tricks your owners of
Flaming homo
Yeah, he's like, yeah, I know okay
So yeah, yeah, what else?
I'm sorry, but just keep that shit to yourself. I'm trying to see that
Tell dude, oh my oh my god
What the fuck now I do chill chill. That's not legal. That's your wife. What the fuck?
No, it was not it was not everything's covered. Everything was covered. Oh
my goodness
Author it was all covered. No, we saw it. No, there was no side balls
Everybody's fucking. Oh my goodness
Arthur, what's wrong? What's wrong?
The only person that likes that is that fucking that weirdo from California, but he she
That's me the other one is weird or the one that one's a change in sex that one doesn't know what the fuck he she they then is
Thank you, five dollars again for me Jimmy's panel and do a speedo jumping jacks, okay
Make it 50. I'll do it. I'll be right back Arthur talking to the chaper second. What's that get?
join join the panel there and do it okay I'll talk to the chat for one second I'll be right back
in two minutes give me two minutes all right everybody head over there bro everybody head over
yo this is gonna be crazy all right I'm gonna start promoting this shit everybody go to groovy Jimmy
psyche will be poor not poor bound but he's gonna fucking show the thumb I repeat
Go to groovy jimmy's channel. I will give you the channel's name. It is called groovy jimmy corporation
three space of words
groovy jimmy corporation and
He is going to fucking show the thumb again. I repeat
groovy jimmy corporation. He is going to show the thumb
Groovy Jimmy Corporation, he is going to show the thong.
Psyche is going to show the thong.
Groovy Jimmy Corporation, that is the channel's name.
Again, I repeat, Groovy Jimmy Corporation.
Psyche will be showing the thong.
We already got four people over there, five.
Five people over there.
Groovy Jimmy Corporation.
Psyche will be joining the band and he will be showing thong.
Again, I repeat
Groovy Jimmy Corporation psyche is going to be on panel and he is going to show some
Groovy Jimmy Corporation
Groovy Jimmy Corporation three spaced out words
There you go. We got 11 people over there 11 people
There's 61 over there in the chat live
There was all about you
Go go go everybody groovy jimmy corporation. I don't know if I want to pull a bomb that you're not
Sure, I want you. I know I'm not gonna show I'm gonna show anything, but I mean I'll show something
Just show the phone just like yo groovy like hey, I'm real quick. I want to see what do you think about the flag?
And then you know
Okay, traveling gypsy traveling gypsy don't do not rewind please don't rewind dude. Come on. You're not gonna go
No, I have a 27 people my own chat right now
Those people had all headed over there. They got it's okay. There was 50 of people over there now. There's 66 waiting for you over there
Well, I think we'll get more alcohol and tobacco
I was I was in an American
That was in the chat, bro
I was in the chat. He's walking back. He's moonwalking. I was in the chat everybody
That was in the chat
Okay, no, no, I'll go over there. I'll go over there. Yeah, I'll just one second one second
No, you already said fucking two minutes fucking five minutes ago. I was in the fucking chat, bro
There's already 18 people over there, brother all wait on site
I was in the chat
I was in the mother fucking shit
That was in the chat everybody's not going over there. He's just had it
And I'm looking at Jimmy's channel right now. Nope. He ain't showing up
That was in the chat
Everybody hit the thumbs down button thumbs down button everybody
Bones down button everyone. Come on
Okay, let's spin the thumbs down. I'm gonna do this like
I really thought he was in the head over there
My fault. My fault. My fault. Everybody hit the thumbs down. Hit the dislike.
That would have been YouTube history. That would have been great.
Uh-oh. He's next age.
He's backstage oh
Shit he's backstage. Yeah, he's backstage. Oh
Shit he's backstage is there. He's not he's there. We will go
The thumbs up bro, it's the thumbs up
They'll be with the chat
It's not it's not for more a guy it was it was just it was just for fun. It was for fun. You liked it
Yeah, it's not for bombing. It's not for more. I was worried. I'm fully closed. I'm completely closed
That was fun, though. Thank you for recommending that
Right I
Just wish you were more quicker with it. Just like you know spread eagle, you know, I know I should I should
Yeah, cuz you said I got a request then he was like
It was fun. It was fun. Everyone liked that. It was fun. Hey, thank you, time. Thank you, time. Thank you. It was fun. It was fun. It's all a good fun. It's all a good fun. There's no side ball. There's nothing.
That'd be that he's in the chat that he's in the chat
It's just like this is funny
I read it
You know what? It's not porn about me, but it's like it's still shocking and like exciting
It's like it's like a proper combination because you're not getting in trouble on the channel
So it's not like oh you have to keep the person off, but it's like it's talking. It's still shocking
Yeah
No, you're useless. Thank you have more balls than straight men
That's crazy, you have more balls than fucking half of the straight men in the chair. I
Get it. I get it
Yeah, I
Will help everyone's ball. So if he has no red I'll get sweep your rent
Oh, okay. I have to go to one third in the afternoon. I think go to the store a minute
I'm gonna go on a bike, you know
I'll put it on. I'll put it on live for you. That was a little funny. That was funny. Okay. Good. I just want to make sure
It was funny. Well, it was funny. Yeah, how far are you from all those riots?
There's a riot. Like there's one that's like the I was in the city
I was born in because it's like a few minutes away. They're at the mall. There are
Ice ages or there's military at the mall right now. So I don't know everyone's tell me go over to the mall like well
Smelly, thank you smelly. Thank you so much
Thank you guys. You're awesome
Thank you time. Thank you smelly. Thank you so much. I appreciate that because people are just I mean looting, right?
Yeah, I mean it's like
What's going they're just stealing it's not even a protest just looting
Know it's ridiculous. I mean, it's like, but you know
We were having these things in Los Angeles where it's like they would just put on the internet
Oh go to this store right now and
You can you can just you like a rob the store and people were doing it and it was like there's like a thousand the people
There's all these flash mobs and stuff. So people will just
Go where they're told to go and stuff, but oh
Well, I'm gonna get I'm gonna go to the store
I didn't put my belt on Asian metal. Yeah, thank you guys. Thank you for the donations. By the way, thank you
This is the speed has been paid for the five times over. Thank you so much. Thank you so much. That's awesome
I see good to hear good to hear
You can put it away now, right? Nobody wants to see it anymore. Thanks
Our agency Arthur you see side balls. You didn't see side balls. Did you I?
Saw like the current the like the wrinkly part. Yeah. Oh my god. There's wrinkly
Well, my balls are old. I have old balls my young guy, but I have old balls
They're hanging like fucking six inches down. Yeah, I know it's embarrassing. It's embarrassing
I don't like to show them very often, but
You know, I don't know. The testicles hang more than the fucking penis itself. Crazy, huh?
Hey Arthur dear balls hang low do they wobble to and fro can you time in and not can time in a bow
Can you throw them over your shoulder like a continental soldier your balls hang low that sounds like a
Like a rap song you know that rap song yeah
Because you know the rap song
Yeah, I know that one, but I don't know if you know what I'm talking about. It's like let your chain hang low let it wobble to the flow
Yeah
You know that song. Yeah, I said, I but I don't have a chain so I just I'll have his balls and so
Also, you do know the song see your way, and you know that song. That's crazy
I'm 1981 Arthur. I know I know I grew up to talk was like my I was like 14 years old
He was to talk without I know all these songs. Oh
Shit, you were born 1981
Yes, I'm very old
Dude, why do you look like you're fucking like from the 50s?
Look at him for the fifties. I like at least seven like 89 years old. They hold the 50. No, that's three years older
So for you as a 70 years old. Are you?
44 I don't like 75
You need to start shaving man. You need to start shaving
Are you doing a donate for for a full shave I can go to the Mexican barbershop right now
It's in the Mexican barbershop
I can't you need to start saving bro. You know what I do because I myself people say I look for old for my age
So that's why I make sure I shave every single morning
There is not a morning. I do not shave
But Arthur what do you shave use your face or you shave everything my entire face your entire body
My entire face my neck my face your hair your hair from the neck down. I'm just harry in general
Yeah, is your is your bush shrimp always always once a week
It once a week you in the shower, or do you do it? Just stay on the couch shower shower, brother. Okay?
Can I you send me a picture of it? What the fuck?
Listen, it was just one time. No, not yet. It's not in dick pics. This is the bush
I just want to see this though. I'll send you a photo of the fucking razor
Yeah, send me photo the razor. I just want to see the horticulture
Can I see it one time?
Dude, I'm not gay, bro. I'm not I know you're not gay. Don't be gay. You guys. Yeah, you'll be gay
I'm not fucking very boy. Why are you so homophobic very very?
I have a picture of Barry's butt and his is a wiener. What the fuck I do you send me both
No, dude, I'm not I'm not confused nor am I, you know, not sure what I am. I know what I am
But damn sure that'd be crazy for me to send some photo like that some gay guy
No, it wasn't it was nice. It was like a nice
It was a bubble, but yeah, very sick, right?
We've all seen it very sensitive everybody now you see look this cuz bear doesn't know how to treat women the right way
You know, he thinks sending a dick pic is what is what they want. No female wants a dick pic
It's all about teasing
The dude sends a dick pic they get turned off. They don't they don't get aroused like we do when we see fucking pussy your fucking tits
Okay, well, I'm gonna be on my bike right now. Are you see here at hang around or for me to my Arthur?
Hey after a few minutes while I go to the store
Can you or no?
Okay, perfect
But just don't turn off the camera
Do not turn off the camera
Yeah, women don't want to see no dick no dick pic
You know you got to show them like
You know you wearing pants and then just that you're hard, you know so I'm showing a photo of that
I'll show them just a dick. You don't want to see
Women don't get turned on I'm by no dick pic
You know
There is an auditory woman
You know women want to see the viny arms the viny hands
Not the viny dick. Come on now
Women in the check you can you can you agree am I wrong?
Am I wrong when I say that like you women you women prefer
A dude sending you like, I don't know, him, him hard, but wearing pants.
Am I wrong? Am I wrong, Chet?
Fucking sending the dick back to a woman ain't gonna do shit to me.
They're not like us. They're not like us. They're not the ender thaws.
Well, I'm like probably I'm like 5% nanothel. He's my forehead. I'm like a little bit
That's fine. You're probably Zae's cousin. I might be. Hey, Lenore, what are you out here?
Lenore, what are you doing?
You see her?
What are you doing Lenore? I see you over there
Give him a bike Arthur. Yeah, I thought you live like in the fourth fifth floor. You live right there
Lenore the adored hey run
Turn my bike. Oh, yeah, that's a bougie. I sure to wear in there, man. I know
There you go
Hey, right there. Are you here? Yeah
Okay
Look give me a huge favor there's like
Not fall right do not fall
My nuts, what about my nuts? No, do not fall. I won't fall
They said put my nuts up. No, no, no, no
Too fast brother you're going too fast
This guy doesn't wear a helmet and he's going 50 miles an hour. What a maniac. What a maniac
You wear a helmet when you ride a car. No, I don't do it now. Hi. How are you sir? You can't compare a bike to a car
It is nowhere near as safe do you understand that it's like do you understand that?
Okay
Lenore the whore
Oh my god, he fell he fell like Chad he fell
Chad he fell he broke the phone damn it he broke the phone
My speedo just broke my butt, okay.
Oh, come on, Louie.
His ass cheeks are eating the fucking phong, look, Chad.
I literally made it in like 30 seconds.
I'm not gonna fast my bike though.
It's not fast.
Okay, oh my god, I gotta...
Okay.
Yeah, psyche
Yeah, do you know Michael Jackson's pronouns?
Do you want to know Michael Jackson's pronouns
Hello
Oh
Yeah, you would check you guys want to know Michael Jackson's pronouns
came back
they weren't there still are they there
thank you do you want to know michael jackson's pronouns
grand yep no i'm just trying to lose my phone sorry
again do you know michael jackson's pronouns it was him her him she or i don't know what is it
All right, fuck me, that wasn't funny in our mind.
All right, whatever.
There you go, guys.
We're going back home.
I got alcohol for the day.
Cigars.
Thank you got that old money, you know my boy rich rich
Yo Psyche, I miss your intro dude. I gotta be honest. I miss your intro.
we chase with love hoping for chance to dance the mystery of mysteries
it's a great song it's a great song yeah yeah yeah
thank you for it thank you for it
how do you mic? hey stand on it just just use that intro song bro
fuck it i think allied and you are finally in good hands
I don't know about all that, but I think you know, I think he's had a change of heart. I think just stop fucking around with him
I'm not fucking around
You should say
All right. Well, I don't know if you're listening, but um
This is what you should say to allied and I quote
Hey allied
Listen, I hope that we can mend the fences. I bend the knee to you
I will no longer talk bad about you
And I will no longer
Make false promises to you
Allied I bend the knee. I hope that we can move on
And I can become a better person
Here's why I disagree. Here's why I disagree with that. I never get into the ally and everyone's soul to them
I never talked about him
He did it to me
But what am I apologizing to him?
What am I bowing to?
All right, I bow I need to God
That's it. No, I get that. I agree. I agree. I agree. Thank you. I didn't do anything to ally
I didn't do anything literally I did nothing
He just came here for all the trouble. Yeah, I agree. So
We're all good. We're all good. I got more cigars. I got more alcohol. Maybe at least we'll go on today
Guys, you have fun last night that we have fun like this. I I used to the video
Yeah, you guys hopefully it wasn't a bit that embarrassing. I don't know. I
Don't know
Is it embarrassing, I don't know what's that I should have everything
What's that
What's that it's just a car
I'm trying to find my I vape maybe I was in there in the vape. I don't look I think my Dave's out
Arden you ever had a bill in this car out there?
No
Can I pull you one?
Okay, guys
Can we sing the song again? Yeah, all right, let's do it
You know begin it
The night the stars showed up for show
Star shine so bright that these ends unfolds. There's
magic in her
This is what the future holds.
Dance to the mystery.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh.
Well, you gotta go slow with that.
Tarot move.
Ta-da.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
I would make a little song I make I would make out to you with that
Sometimes get the fuck out of here, dude. What the fuck is wrong with you? I ain't no faggot cut the bullshit, bro
I told you Saturday already cut the fucking bullshit. I ain't fucking around with that
No, I'm falling low. I fall in love with you. You're my
is wrong with you, bro
There's something
I don't fuck around with that shit. No, no, you like you
Yes, it is
No, it is cute
Yes, it is dude. Hey
I don't want to start speaking louder you dude. Stop. Oh shit
We be sensory. Oh, stop getting so mad. Oh, don't be so let me so it's just deep the bullshit
I'm telling you right now, dude. Cut the fucking bullshit or else. I'll get my fucking cut your neck
He's not mad. Oh, okay. Go away. Go away. Go away. He's not mad. He's not mad. He's just he's he's oh look at here the ten of wands
Here's look at and there's like the snow white
You know the queen but the ten of wands means a lot of activity right the ten of wands a
Lot of stuff going on a lot of activity
Okay, I'll read you from the book. So I love this bill this bill in the book. Yeah, so it's a ten of wands. Okay, it says
Okay, ten of ones. Because with success comes responsibility. If you're feeling burdened
or overwhelmed by a new role, remember that even the greatest villains have henchmen
to help carry through their plans. It's time to take some pressure off yourself by assigning
some of the workload to others. Maybe you're a little overwhelmed. What do you want? What do
Dude, please stop
You're calling me names now now you're being not but you but you're like literally like you're like I want to make out like dude
Come on, bro. I do. I do. I know. No, I'm in love with you
Are there I all I know is your foot. I just know what your foot looks like and you're gonna sexy foot
horn
Right am I wrong?
Dude, I've camped up numerous times. I nurse and I don't remember
Okay, it's fine. You're welcome to repeat. You love the old hag and I'm but she's actually
Can I can I tell you I know somebody that likes you who does who likes me nobody likes me
I'm always afraid to join panels. They miss swag or
Well, so I go so gore come on over
You're welcome over you're welcome over
I'm trying to tell him I'm like dude like stop like stop using fake accounts. Just
You know psyche and the people you know, it's all right. You're free of an ally now. You're an ally rogue
Good afternoon
What do you think we're what is going on? Oh, is it this guy that Eldon I cooked already? I
Just think that if you play with ounce would open I will sing it
Rogue did you see my speedo? I
Did not see your speedo. You want to see it? No. No. No. No. I'm just thinking. Yeah. You said yes, okay?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I think he said yeah, I heard I heard you the word yes, okay? No, I'm okay like okay
So look this guy he's gay
No, motherfucker. Don't do that
No, I'm not I'm just gonna show it. I'm not showing anything. It's a speedo. Okay. I'll pull it up a little bit
There you want to see just say yes, just say yes
Row good
Pull the speed. Oh, I'll pull it up pull it up pull it up all the way pull it up all the way
It was just a side, it was a side cheek. It was a side cheek.
Yeah!
Are you done? Have you finished your performance of gayness?
Well, he's fucking gay.
I mean, I like gay.
Yeah! What the fuck, bro?
But he's gay as fuck.
Yeah! No, no, no!
What the fuck
Yo, what the fuck
No, no, I think I think it's putting it back on so you can come back on panel brother
Sorry, oh my goodness
I think he fucking got a wedgie.
Who is this? Who is on the other line?
This is Eldo.
No, it's not.
I already cooked you last time. I don't know why you're back.
Who is it?
I'm Eldo. Remember you were flirting with the girl on the panel and I told you dude, fuck off.
No, you're always trying to flirt with every single girl
You're always trying to flirt with every single girl, but this time you're trying for a beta and I told you dude
No, hey, there was a woman that I was not trying to put this beta. That's how you know your mistake
You were trying to you were trying I don't know you were acting like boyfriend
You were trying to correct your ways you were trying to take her away from the streets. Oh, yeah
So, yeah, so this is Arthur
There you go
Well, Arthur, hope you having a magnificent
Wednesday my friend
Well, I hope you stop flirting with women online. I
Don't I have a woman by my side at the moment. Why what what's I do? What did I do that you won't know man? What did I do?
What did you do? Yeah, psyche he wants you to lift the thong again. He missed it
By the side will you wear that thong like on the on the passenger seat?
Road to see he wants you to pull it up on the sides. Oh my god
Okay, that's actually
That is that's not that's a piece of a it's a phone. It's foam
Speedos. Oh my god
That was just a phone. What do you think? Roe? Is it good?
No, I think that you're gay as a motherfucker and that's
But just don't bring that game is upon me you understand
It was a guy who said he wants to see a phone
Hi, I'd be there
I don't know
You might see more you want to see more
He what did he just say beat as a crush on him get the fuck out of here
Yo, everybody heard that right? Yeah, no, she does not at all. Yeah rewind that shit. Yeah, she does
I don't know
Hey, Ro what's up?
What the hell broke
Bro, this is birthday it is tomorrow yours. Yeah
Happy birthday Gemini. It's June 12 birthday. Yes, sir. Thank you very much. Thank you
I'm I took off I decided to take off from now until Monday to just celebrate my birthday
Okay, let's do it. Let's do it. We'll do it. Oh, I'll give you a special birthday present on June
It's not nice video June 12
You know, let me see it's called I turned 38 years old motherfucker 38. I don't feel 38
At all. Okay, so so rogue nomad is really quick
So it says June 12th the day of buoyant optimism
Optimistic expansive those born on June 12th generally operate under the assumption that things will be going fine
Rarely will they give it to a sense of defeatism even when circumstances present a rather gloomy outlook
However, their cheerful exterior can at times hide its troubled inner life
Though they meet life's challenges squarely such worldly concerns may draw an inordinate amount of energy away from their own problems
They must be aware that unresolved personal issues do not undercut their endeavors
June 12 people can be very generous
giving people only
when they feel it's warranted.
Though optimist, they are realistic and objective individuals
not to be approached for a handout
and generally of the opinion that God helps those that help themselves.
This attitude applies in relation to their children and parents as well, and although
they are there for their families, they may appear a bit hard at times, particularly since
they are rather judgmental.
In truth, those born on this day are extremely dutiful and responsible individuals who understand
that too much kindness kills independence.
Too much nurturing cycles growth.
You and 12 people are interesting blend of pragmatists and idealists. They're naivete
Manifest in relation to themselves not to the world at large which they treat quite realistically
Unfortunately, those born this day don't use don't see the world as a mirror for self-understanding
Too often, they surround themselves with people who perpetuate and reinforce an unrealistic image.
Thus, June 12 people's grace, difficulty lies in perceiving themselves objectively.
Absolutely accurate.
People born on this day are happiest when in motion.
They love to fly, to drive, in short, to travel for its own sake.
Too often, they feel that by mourning, they can leave their troubles behind, but of course, this is not the case.
Many June 12 people can benefit greatly from centering themselves and withdrawing periodically
from their numerous involvements.
More highly evolved June 12 people can't succeed in facing up to their difficulties.
After they weather their initial stock, their depression that might follow, they can emerge
as stronger, more aware individuals of the purpose.
Make good parents and friends in the sense of being fun entertaining
Never boring though valuable talented people. They need to temper their optimism. I
Come to terms with the more problematic aspects of their personality
Well, that was extremely accurate and as I know you're a professional reader, so I deeply appreciate you sharing
Thank you. You're welcome. Happy birthday. Happy birthday. Happy birthday. I really appreciate it. Thank you very very much
But on my heart you're welcome
You're welcome. My dad was a Gemini my sister's a Gemini. I've a Jimmy loved it. Yeah, I know I know
You did you see I beat a speedo. I did a speedo speedo flash on Jimmy's channel. You see that beta
Three one, but you know the girl that I'm with right now. She's also a reader. She she read my cards
She's right now next to me and the last time that she did a reading. Hey, can you tell me what did you read?
What did you tell him?
See I don't remember. Oh
You know when you do a reading you don't hold the information because it's for the other person
You're like a bedroom nomad with your wife
No, that's definitely on my wife
Okay, so so rogue no man's girlfriend. Do you see me in my speedo?
My speedo has powers, you know, he's whispering since they know
Tell him what what what did you say him on this video? Oh?
Yeah, I did see the speedo
Okay, thank you. Thank you so much. Yeah
You know I
Try I don't even try it's just it's I'm just naturally gifted Jimmy appearances. Yes. Thank you guys
Hey, how's this guy rogu? This guy rogu no man. How is this guy? Is he is a good good boy friends or no?
He just picked me up off the street
He's picked the street. He got you. He found me in the street. He just brought me into his house
Okay
Yeah, I thought I thought rogue nomad was making girl voices again. It is really a woman next time
What are you doing on a panel when you have a woman next to you rogue nomad?
We'll get laid
He got bored a little break. Can you stop them? Stop them like for me just one time really hard
You know to stop them. He's been really mean. I
Did I slap them?
Okay, I'm kicking on the balls to now later on later on I mean just like just a little bit nice no no
What are you guys doing on here?
I don't even know what this is.
I don't know what I'm doing here. None of us really know what we're doing here.
I'm running around the speedo for 12 hours.
That's all I know.
Can you show it to her? Can you show it to her?
Yes, I can.
You want to see
He's got a new speedo from like a fan and he's modeling it. He's pretty
You like it, it was good it was good Robin how mad you what do you think?
He loved it. He loved it. He loved it. He wasn't looking.
He wasn't looking?
Rogue, you are looking? Rogue?
I know. I think that is a nice, I think that is,
Speedo produces high quality swimming gear.
Come on, stop it.
He's been wearing that.
Is your game? Oh, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I say I'm sorry.
Harley has to take a ride in the back of it.
Yeah, I can ride, I can ride bitch with you.
Yeah, imagine that.
If anybody that knows me, I just pull up
and there's this fucking guy in the back of it.
I'll be like, I'll be like that, I'm back.
No, I might as well just fucking put a bullet in my skull.
What?
Rogue, no, Matt, please, please, please.
No, guys.
Can you hear him?
Yeah, yeah.
Rogue, no, Matt, happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you, Sean.
Oh, thank you so much, Vita.
Happy birthday, Rogue.
No, Matt.
I thank you.
Happy birthday.
Oh, happy birthday.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no, I'm doing. That was my birthday present. That was it. That was it. Happy birthday, Rodin. No, man.
It's rewind back. It's rewind back. Oh, she's like it. Oh my god, I'm dead. I'm good. Oh my god. I had to put on my mute so I don't cough.
She has the most perfect hits that I'm talking on right now.
How are you talking if you're sucking on kids? Can you hear me right now?
What's in your mouth, rhodometh?
Psyche, put your shorts in his mouth.
I'm just kidding.
Oh, no, man. Do you want to see? No, I am sucking on titties. Why will I see that?
What's that noise? I hear what's that noise? It's strange noise. Oh my god, why is my garage open?
Because they know he's a little man sucking titties.
Yeah, you scared beat away you scared beat away, but I'm like here because my I don't know look at my legs one I
Don't my legs are here
We're fine, we're fine wants to play too. He does he always
That's like that I always have to tell him no, I'm not gonna play mother fucker
See look at him
It's okay. Stop that shit. No, it's not gay. It's not gay. No, I'm not stopping Doug Doug. Doug loves it Doug loves it
Not gay. It's not good. Oh, no, no
Where are you?
He's in California. I can't leave the house. There's a riots outside. I can't even leave the house
So he's only
Yes, I'm just I'm stuck in my speedo
You know this girl she has a cat from Russia
She has an actual catch Sabrina from Russia. This motherfucker has seven cats. Oh my god seven cats
Oh, it was a cat home tricks. Do I come over here to add it?
It's funny because he has a cat that has big as balls and he calls them marbles because his balls are so big
There was marbles marbles
Oh, hey, Lenore, you can say hi.
So Lenore, yeah.
Lenore.
That's Lenore.
Oh.
The black kid.
Mm.
You're just sitting up there?
Yeah.
Mm.
What's wrong?
That's Lenore.
Lenore jumped up.
Did you saw?
Hi.
You heard me talking to, sure.
You're talking to Robe Nodemack?
Yeah, Lenore, look at Lenore.
Where's Marble's?
Marble?
Oh, Marble's outside.
Marble's outside.
Marbles is out getting pussy in the neighborhood. She's the best look. She's right there. They're sitting up on my shoulder
You're purring you're purring. Well this girl has a cat called Sabrina that is beautiful and it's actually from Russia
Right. Oh
Tell them about your cat. She was rescued
Who's rescued all?
Yeah, it's like is it black cat like the brain of the teenage witch or
She's white gray
fluffy and
just so
The temperament is so cute
Yeah, the north's purring right you're purring good. You go down the nor you jump on my back
No, Edwards. No Edwards. You love her so much. Yes. She's a sweetheart. You're sweetheart. You jumped on my back. Can you give me?
Hey, give me kiss. Oh
Oh, give me a kiss. Yeah, you have to hold her head
That's that's Lenora
Yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh your ear. Hey, you like that. You like that
Marble here has some big-ass balls
He does that's miss Lenora. Look what I go down Lenora. Good. I'm good. There you go. There you go. She went down
Oh my gosh, I'm playing with some big-ass stades right now
I don't. I don't. I don't.
I don't. I don't. I don't. I
don't. I don't. I don't. I
You love her. I love Lenore too. Hey Lenore. You're gonna kiss. Can we kiss this?
I know I want to know everything I want to know everything. What do you want to know about them?
How big are his balls?
More than a mouthful. Okay. Well
Well, you're awesome. You're awesome. You know, I think you play for him pretty up to this guy and this guy
He's a weird. He's so he's crazy guy
comes into my chat
He tells me to get in a speedo and then he says, oh, no, I didn't he said I don't want to see and then he looks
I know he was looking I
Never I never said you looked you looked. Yes. You said you said don't show me and then you looked
Oh, no, no, no, no, don't show your butthole one
What I care was Kate. Hey, that's Lenore
We're gonna sit about my shoulder is you guys have pets
Is it real humans
It's really humans. I need to pull my pants one. No, good job. What is this?
He did look he glanced at the screen rode no mask over he glanced at the screen or no
Yeah, he did
He look yeah, he watched the whole time. I know I know he did
It's okay, you're not gay road nomad. You're straight. You're you're literally sucking on our titties in my chat
I am how can you tell?
Yeah, I heard your mouth was full. I
recognize this
They are big as it is
Kate nearly pissed herself that we now had Arthur
Screaming howling because of the speedo. I know guys. Thank you. Thanks. This thing. Thank you easy for the speedos
I'm gonna find you outfit
No, no, you're shouting. Oh, no, what are you doing? Oh?
Good
She won't she won't no come over my shoulder
Wait, what are they? They are literally 38 D's
Hi, but they're at least 38
You got a mouthful you got a mouthful of Robo man like second they suck in the titties. Okay
No, what do you think of Arthur?
Nor they are what is he doing? Oh my god? I don't know about it guys. This is a lot on the show guys
This is what's going on here?
It says
You're getting distracted
She's going to the bathroom. Did you say something wrong? No, I did it. She just has to go to the bathroom. She has to go
You gotta go you gotta go Lenore. Do you say something wrong? Would you say the road? No man's girlfriend?
No, she's done my girlfriend
My girlfriend, okay
My friend your lady friend from a benefit
Yeah, we make we make love
I
Heard heard them in your mouth. Yeah, they were in my mouth
Natural all natural
Well, it was my birthday. So I decided, you know, I was supposed to work like Thursday Friday
Then Saturday and Sunday, I was supposed to take a course and I said, you know what fucking I'm gonna cancel work
Thursday and Friday, and I'm gonna move the course one week out
I'm just gonna fucking party until Monday morning. So you're stuck with me motherfucker. Sorry
So we're so rogue rogue. I haven't birthday present for you. Okay, I'll do your
It's just lay down on the bed and close your eyes and I'll be in the room in five minutes
What will you do?
We clean everything your eyes will be your eyes will be closed. You won't be able to clean everything up
Well, you just press yes, yes the room up. Oh, I'll clean you. I'll clean you the living room after that. Yes
Yes, that that's actually yeah, I'm pressing dude that the dishes. Oh
Really, I mean, yeah, I would love that. Thank you so well
Yeah, I mean I I hundred percent just clean the living room
Clean them do the dishes clean the kitchen like if you don't mind they
There's some stuff and after after you after you all that I'm gonna clean you I'm gonna clean you after everything. Is that okay?
No, it's not okay because that's why I have this beautiful woman by my side
No, but you're gonna have your eyes closed
She's bad he's very lovey-dovey
See mill is he milking it? Oh no, no matter don't milk your girlfriend, okay?
Are you milking where's I don't know he's on my back
He's on your back. Okay. Okay. It's okay. I don't know. Okay. I don't know what's going on. Okay. I don't know what's going on. Oh
Kind of road no mad look at look at road no man. Look at Lenore the cat
She has a cat too. She has a Sabrina Sabrina
Yeah, she has a brain out of cat.
I can't, I kiss too.
Oh, he's mimicking me.
Yes, he is.
I hear a dog barking. Wait, is this dog barking?
You can hear them? There's like four of them out there.
Yeah, I hear dogs barking.
Oh, you're kissing me. You're kissing. They're very distracting
What kind of dogs do you have?
big ones
Give a big one. How do you tell me? How do you train road Nomad? How do you train this guy? He's uncontrollable. How do you do it?
How do you train me? What?
He's not trainable. Yep. He's not a trainable
You gotta accept it
Your girlfriend has a newspaper. She smacks you on the ass with the newspaper, right?
No, she
You had no idea what's going on right now. I
Can hear I hear I can imagine
Here's a grab
That was who you are
Nope, you're looking pussy. Are you looking at this?
You tell him. What's going on? What's he doing? What's he doing? What did he do? What did he just do?
Where's your face or where's your face rodeo man? You sound like you're my
Where's the phone by
I hear a licking his down by her face. It's by her. Okay. You're kissing. You're kissing there
Let's kiss on that cheek. You're just kissing your cheek guys. No something much better. What's he doing baby?
Oh my god, that sounds I hear a sound you tell
Tell him what am I doing?
Beautiful girl
What do you do it? Well guys, what do you do it guys?
This is a PG-13 where he is straight. What's going on here? Here's slurping sounds
I
Don't want to tell me she doesn't want to reveal it's a secret. Yeah, she doesn't you imagine I should respect it
Oh, what was that?
She's he's he has a lollipop. She had a lollipop
Down
Her mouth is full Arthur her mouth is full road no man leave her alone
I
Don't know what I don't know what they're doing. I don't know what they're doing. What are they doing guys?
What's going on?
And here's sounds
What kind of a sound describe it
Sounds like
We represent the Lollipop Guild, the Lollipop Guild, the Lollipop Guild, and in the name of the Lollipop Guild,
we wish to welcome you to Munchkin Land.
Am I right or wrong?
Not even close.
Okay, never mind, I don't know what to talk about.
Yeah.
What's it? Well, why don't you hear a slurping? What are you slurping on? Are you drinking a slurpee?
He's drinking a drink. Oh, yeah
What are you drinking?
Water this water, okay
Having a ball. Okay, he said in the bottle
It's in the bottle. What are you drinking? What are you drinking? What are you drinking road? No matter? What are you drinking?
You're she said you're hitting the bottle. I'm drinking this
Strawberry lemon smear it off. What are you? What are you drinking Arthur?
Arthur's your mouth full
No, no, sorry. It's hard. We'll know that we'll know Matt. It's a road. No, Matt
What beat his back beat his back? Yeah, I talked to me. I don't know what to say, but uh, I'm shocked
It has this thing. What are they doing? What are they doing me? I don't know. I just you're like
There's your slippery sounds
She's just she's just babying him
No one's a big baby. I mean
Stand at your baby. Oh, no
Do you give room at a cat bath, you know a cat bath is no, yeah, yeah, they lick themselves. Yeah
This is where I like rogue nomad from his head to his toe and you take photographs and then blackmail me
Yeah, do that for him nomad girlfriend. Can you do that?
Like get some pictures. Yeah, so you can blackmail uh rogue nomad
Yeah
No, we don't do that. It's okay rogue nomad. We don't do that. Okay. We won't do that. We won't. We know we won't
Come blackmail. I'm just gonna
Road no matter you're there
Yes, I'm here. They do you seem so surprised that a woman that I'm with is somehow kind and loyal to me
Yeah, what does she do? What is what it? What does she do into your road? No, man. I hear a sport brings out
She doesn't need to do anything to me with the body that she has
I'll do everything
Yeah, but the busy hands
He's busy hands
Yeah, he loves he like so I know about rogue no man. He loves titties. He just loves them, right?
He likes titties and speedos
Do you see my speedo's rogue no man? Are you looking at a screen?
I'm gonna show you something afterwards after you
Very few women have the kind of tits that the woman that I'm playing with
I'm enjoying with nobody cares wrong. No, I'm not like
Look at the kids. Look at the speedos
You're gonna you're gonna turn off your new girlfriend. Okay? Hey
How is it what do you think we're gonna make what do you think tell me how you thought yeah, that's irrelevant to me because 38
Yeah, it's 38 double these now 38 double these are a league of their own and that's when you get my attention
That's when you get my respect
Hey, I'm breast and let's hey
This used to be my playground
This used to be the place
$100 each shot if anybody wants to roll no mouse pictures send me a hundred dollar cash shop for each one
What is it? What's in the picture though? I mean, yeah, yes, everything everything
One thousand for the third picture. I'm just kidding with you. No, I just wanted to show you this thing right here
I bought at CBS today. I thought about you guys hold up. I think it's gonna suck
Just because it was like pretty cheap. It was only 1499 but it says
Uh
Shorty oh charades. Oh charades. I see shorty
today boomer gen X and millennial and then
Gen Z generation
What is it? But why is Gen Z and I have arms, but what's wrong? I don't know. I have no idea
Oh my god guys you right there. That's me. We're my hands
Nobody has arms
Look at look at look at those muscles
Are they like that they're like big big hour blasts on his on his arms
Oh my god, I think I got ripped off. This is so stupid.
Down, down. Request, re-k, re-question.
We got it. Look at what it's like in there. It's like, this is like child play or something.
Okay. There's dice in there. And then-
There's dice? Let's play.
Don't need the dice. We don't need it.
So your choice, whatever. I don't know what this is, but I'll see. I'll ask questions.
Let's see.
How do you know which one is for a bloomer than millennials? I don't fucking know.
I don't I don't know. What are you a rogue number? What are you and your girlfriend? Are you boomers or your millennials?
Millennials. Yeah
So let's see. Sorry. I got any pull my pants. I'm sorry
No worries
He feels like he needs me. Yeah, I feel I felt too relaxed. I felt too relaxed. I felt too relaxed
Okay, this millennial this millennial couple both music or okay
This millennial couple both music and artists famously married in 2002 and divorced in 2008
Just a beeper and Kate Winslet. No, I'm not sure. No, no, you know, you know, what do you?
These are stupid and hard questions at the same time things. It's hard. It's hard
It's like a Nick Lachey and Jessica Simpson. What the fuck? I don't want to go into the
Hey, hey, is chicken on the sea? Is that tuna or is that chicken chicken on the sea?
It's tuna. It's tuna. Okay. I'm hungry for lunch
I didn't know chickens are swimming the sea. So I don't know
Yeah, yes, thank you
They do. Oh
Just for me chickens, which I mean
You guys these questions are gonna be so fucking challenging. I can't wait till we play them. We're gonna play with thank you later
Yeah, they're pretty challenging
Melly got that one
Hey, hey, remember Nick and Jessica newlyweds and they were so cute and then the divorce. It was so sad
Remember Nick and Nick and Jessica. I always thought he was really cute. He was really I do you I use cute
He's very cute. Yeah, what is this song? I'll sing a song. He's a good song
Remember Nick to say a song home
Yeah, hey, can we do karaoke? Yeah
I know you make you you wanted you want that song for everybody with you're so predictable
We know you yeah, well, I mean at least I'm good at one song, okay
So are you ready?
Maybe he can dance
Alexa, play with arms wide open
No you can't play, you can't play music
You can't play music, you're just singing it
With arms wide open
Over the sunlight
Welcome to the place
I'll tell you everything
Play with my hands wide open
For this big ass city
Now his butthole has changed. He showed you love. He showed you every new thing.
With ass wide open. With legs wide open.
Welcome to the place. Hey, hey, Rogue Nomad, how wide are your legs spread? Rogue Nomad, are your legs spread right now?
Yeah
With arms wide open rogue. No man. Can it trade me? Please? I'll show you everything
with legs wide open
When I once heard the news
To be the man done over
No, no
Ass in the air
He loves it. He loves this song and it's supposed to be like a Christian, I'm sorry Jesus
No, no, man, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
If I had just one wig with legs wide open
Rogue don't man love me so much
Is girlfriends watching with legs wide open
Now it goes?
If I had just one wig
Beautiful.
You're ready now? Thank you. We gotta sing it.
We're your backup singers.
Under them.
Roof
And he lagged like his butt and everything changed
Everything changed, you're brilliant
With legs wide open, turn off the music
Well, you can no man. Yeah. Yes, room. No, man. Where are your feet behind your head? I
Everything I saw everything you say everything. I said them the picture broke no matter of your feet behind your belt
That is
Yeah, he gave me a hundred dollars for it. Yes
We've made your girlfriends take pictures of it when I give I give fifty to your girlfriend. We split it enough
Yeah, well my girlfriend here has 38 double D's I
Know I heard it. I heard them in her mouth. I heard them in her mouth
Is there anyone Jojo? I heard you say
This is what I heard
All natural all natural. It's all natural. Okay. He's like
I
You just got late for the first time in your life like
Road no matter there he's always seen his dick. Oh, you just seen his own dick
He gets laid if he makes up for his girlfriend now his girlfriend. No, I shouldn't say anything
He likes lady. He likes ladies of the night and now we found a real girlfriend for him. So he's retired now. He's retired
I just want to ask rogue domain's girlfriend. How does he smell the clean up nice?
Do you like your freshly sent it? He's like to car to car cologne. What do you smell like? I don't know his smell
He smells good. He smells good. Okay
He's like
But he does
Calvin plan session he sprays it but bunghole
Robe no man, have you already gay experience I want to hear about this
Absolutely not. Like I told you so many fucking times that I'm not a fuck. No, but yeah, so you know you're in a locker room
What happened in the locker room something happened? Oh, yeah, you remember that time in the locker room. Yeah, I remember that one time
Mourn you're you're you're soaking up in the quarterback
Came in the shower with you. Yeah
And he said can we share or like
It's boring. Oh my gosh
Rogue no man. You you play football on baseball, right? You play football baseball. No, neither of them
You didn't are you you're wrestling?
You're wrestling you do wrestling
He did he's not he didn't answer right he's he didn't wrestle so you did the gayest or possible you wrestled did you live tell me
Yes
Yeah, how does it look at his he wears is there where he is wrestling siglin that right now?
Eraser you remember the good smelling erasers
Yeah, they don't know what I think that's what a rogue now a rogue nomads always smells like
erasers
No, like a racer's right. Yeah, it's bubble gum erasers or something. He's no robe nomads smells very good
And he's worried he wears the the wrestling singlet and we're gonna wrestle
We're gonna wrestle robe nomads. Tell me to say yes. We can wrestle one time to say yes
Yes, I
Hear I heard yes. No, he smells fine. He smells but he's I know he smells fine
He smells like acts acts the ex body wash and and Calvin Klein cologne. I know
What the fuck was that we tried?
What's his name Michael saying about me earlier? I
Don't know Michael Michael Michael just you went Michael went insane today. You're Michael
He was he was saying fuck you psyche you say fuck everybody. He was he lost it. He lost it today
At least
I like her. I like her. I like her. I like her too. I like her too. I like her too. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her. We like her.
Mail bath showers, what do they call those? Yeah in the bath house
Rogue don't mind have you ever into the bath if you're rid of the male bath house just a male bath house
It's naked in the locker room. Whatever happens happens. Is that ever happened? No, no, no, okay?
I was I got the trivia's you'll never get them right. Haha. Well, you probably will Google it, but
Yeah, yeah
Persian woman she harasses me. I
Really, I love this most coconut. I really what it's like in pussy punk. I harass you
Yeah, they want this thing down pussy punk
Oh, wait, Robonoma wants to get exposed. That's what he's asking for trying to lie on my ass
Rogue no man. So you never you never had one gay experience like it's not one
You never like we're in a sauna and it's like put your head back and like let the guy do every one
He did
Yeah, it was two guys and one girl so they're balls guys
Two guys
Yeah
The homies can't get some you were you were you were in a Mexican gang bang
I know it's Mexican gang man. It's like all guys and one woman. I know what Mexican gang man. No, you're Mexican, right?
Okay, no, no, no, no, he did he did it Henry you would do pictures
Don't be racist. Okay. It was the Asian guy and a black guy and him. That's it. It was three-stop
It's not a big deal. It happens all the time
Well, no man, how many times do you touch it? How many times you touch tips?
How many times never
Never
He's hesitating. He did. He did. He did. I know he did. He did. He did. He did. I know. He's hesitating. He hesitated. He's going to say it. He just said no. He just said no.
It's okay. It's 2025. It's game 5.
You're so anal nomad. Yeah. Oh no, man. Oh no, man. I've been arrested. I've been arrested. I've been arrested. I've been arrested. We're gonna steal her from you and we're gonna... Never been?
Yeah. Roe, when you got arrested, when you got arrested, what do you have to do? Is it turn around and spread your cheeks, right? I've never been arrested. No. Yes, you have. You have so. No, no. Oh, he's so innocent. I don't believe it.
Yes, you were you arrested. Yeah, he was never arrested
No, it was a misdemeanor. He's not he doesn't have a felony charge
He was he would he'd go to jail
But I dated him in jail. We're like he was my cell he ratted he ratted and they let him go. Yeah
We know his whole story. We know his whole background a rust record
Okay, it's okay
It's June it's called gay pride month. It's like, you know, if you're your allies my birthday is tomorrow
He's born you're born in gay pride month. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, right in the middle of it smack of it. Yeah, but you wish for me to suffer my birthday
No, I don't know. Yeah, you know you can be the top. No, it's very clear that you know
No
Yeah
Rogue no man
No, no, no, I don't I want you I want you to and put a blindfold on you
I'm gonna put a blindfold on you. You'll feel your shirt taking off your shorts are to come down. Just close your eyes
Your girlfriend will be there at the end of it, but I'll be there in the middle of it. Okay
You can ask will you ever I love that? Yeah, I think she she thinks that psyche is a nice guy. He's pretty good
Answer baby
She can answer what she likes
You say yes? I heard a yes?
I think we should kick Rogue Nomad and keep his girlfriend on the panel
I agree
Yeah, yeah, we like her
Rogue, yeah
Rogue, can you take your girlfriend and then phone Rogue?
We don't talk to anyone
We just want your girlfriend
We don't, yeah
I think we're in here at the moment
Oh, wait, wait, it's your birthday
We have to be nice to them, you guys
We do
Answer, please
Answer I don't know what I'm answering
Roots some confused your girlfriend room romance girlfriends very good. I know she's confused because
Robe romance confusing guy
Yeah, remember you remember the time you take a shower if you wrote no mad and I dropped the soap. Oh, I'll never forget that
You know forget that yeah, I remember that too
We take a shower together we did this is clear this is a clear case. What's going on, so I beat it. What's going on?
I only got two minutes. I just want to explain something everybody. This is clear is the bell
First, it was Michael earlier, and now this rogue nomad.
These are guys that aren't happy in their marriages or relationships with their women.
They're clearly in love with Psyche.
They want to get with him.
They just don't want to admit it.
I don't know you, dude, but you're clearly gay.
Just explain to your girl and let her know.
And Michael, I know you're listening to Faggot.
You're the same way, dude.
Psyche loves you.
You love Psyche.
That's not even one else
Do we like he looks good speed he's pretty pretty good-looking no
But he doesn't I don't know
What what did you say we're talking about me wrong no bad we're talking about me
Other guy you mean God I went to that there's a which the mountains
Yeah, the Himalayas
Mountains like greats over there where your speed or area is
Yeah, good early. Look at me
I
Go in the bathroom
You come in, yeah, I got the T-moo, you come in the, you come in the, you come in the bathroom, I'm right there, I said, can I give you an assistance?
Yes, do you want to just say that my birthday, you want me to die on my birthday?
No, why do you wish to worse on yourself? That's horrible, Rosemarie.
Oh my God, it's clearly just one me to die on my birthday.
Nobody wants you to die.
No, you just want me to stop it.
Well, stop crying.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Uh
What the fuck
Thank you, what's your uh, where's your audio?
But he said wait, okay wait
Because he wants me to perish on my birthday
Oh
Yeah, oh
He has made a plan for me to use pass away. Oh my god, what a crybaby
So it's nobody wants you to die on your birthday
We're sure
Acquisition you do your show
Oh my God, you left me with, I'm going to, oh my God, it's like I'm a third wheel on a party at date. Thank you. Come on. Don't leave me alone here with the love birds. Please.
Happy birthday.
Oh, thank you so much. I really appreciate it.
Thank you. Bye.
Thank you.
So yeah, did they go is up that girl like she
Would be to go where'd be to go?
I'm a head blizzard. Hey, they're real no man
Yeah, I'm here
Guys, are we never three summer or not?
Guys, I'm getting bored
Now we're not gonna have yes, yes, you're to close your your close your eyes. You won't know what's happening where
Do you care? Is it okay or no? Road no any information road no matter. It's too weird
Okay, he said I heard him say I heard a yes. I heard a yes
Hello road no mad yes
Yes, okay. Yes. He said yes guys. No. No. Yes. He said yes. He said yes. No. No. No. No. No. Yes. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
You don't like the racer tips. Yeah, I don't like a razor tips a razor tips. I
Like big fucking titties that are soft
How about golf balls you like golf balls? No, I like big you're like golf
You know you like hitting golf balls. I'm gonna hit my golf. No, I like big stuff. Okay. Okay. Okay guys
I love you guys guys. You have guys have fun. I'm gonna leave you guys a little I got guys
I know you're just having fun. Okay, you guys have a fun night, okay?
It sounds very sexy. I mean, I'll join you in 20 minutes. I'll be I'll just knock on the door to stop me in okay, all right
Okay, I love you rodeo man. I love you too my muscle. You're my muscle man. Good night rodeo man's girlfriend
Thank you for putting up with me. I'm not gonna pick up for you. Oh
Yeah
Thank you, look at those muscles enjoy those muscles. You're a lucky woman. There's look at those muscles
Yeah, it's hot
They're real they're real and they're spectacular
Thank you
Thank you, thank you
Hey, don't talk to your mouth full of room. No man. I'll see you later. Okay. I love you. I love you, too. Bye. Bye
Okay
That's his girlfriend. I know it's his girlfriend
Hey, I can talk to scribbles a scribble's wife. She went off tonight
I was on the phone with him for like 20 minutes and he was like, is it there you still the phone me?
I was like, yes, and he got up right away
Lucky you're not getting mod. You're not getting mod Doug muscle pick
It was a nice muscle pick
Guys if he's still in the backstage if I can put it back I'll put it back with her sucking sound
Where's his ears sir
You're here, so they know what boom to push
You know, but I was waiting here a sucking sound
Closed that's why
Yeah, it is my birthday
Happy birthday. Road. No, man. No, man. Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you
Road, no, man. This I have a little birthday present for you. Okay. Road. No, man. No, man. You want it? You want it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Well, that was a happy birthday present because I like you so much. I like you so much. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
You're welcome. You're very welcome. I love you. I love you guys. Okay, you guys have fun first birthday. Okay, you have fun
Okay, it's my birthday
It's his birthday. Yeah, it's my birthday
Happy birthday. We'll do a man's birthday to you close your eyes. I'll be right in there. I'll be in the bedroom in five minutes
Okay, just close your eyes. Okay
It's crazy it's like it's crazy Albeda's in chat when she was talking all this shit about you
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You should have unmodbed her to be honest with you. But she didn't say anything about it. It's fine
Come on
No, no, no, no beat it beat it has like gone on
I wouldn't lie to you
What'd it be to say would be to say something?
How much of a disgusting person you are? Oh, it's okay. I'll do. Did you see my
You're surprised yet. No, no, you want it? You're an elder
No, don't sexually assault me. No, I'm not going to
That's what you're L though
Or you eat you trying to eat sexually assault me. I'm not looking at no, no, no, no driving L though
You're driving yeah, okay, never mind never mind that no one's on you think no one's on
What would you just explain what you was trying to do? What would you try to do you through wine get your wine for those for you?
Yeah, you're confused
Confused Elzo Elzo. Oh, we beat us here. Oh, who the fuck do you think you are Elzo?
Man, I'm just letting her know how much of a snake you are.
That's it.
You mad?
Your snake, I sent it to his fucking face.
And then he came out on my panel,
and he did a strip show, and I forgave him.
Are you jealous?
Yeah, of course.
I'm jealous, Bita.
Hi.
You're just jealous because me and you
could not make a mess, because you're a bitch.
You don't want to mind my damn begging, but you're OK.
Begging what?
Read it.
What did I beg?
I don't do that, you know?
What?
You're going to be another spammer?
Do it.
Begging what?
You're so fucking awesome. I'll say I'm gonna say you was funny too good
really
Also, we already clear that one too. You're trying to you fake
Hold on. Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I don't love it as a doc
You're fake
You came on my panel and you put me in all this kind of fucking bad predicaments
And then you went over there and then you fucking like stab me in the fucking back like a mother
Yeah, I'm doing that. I
don't know. Okay. Okay. Maud.
Maud, take care of it. This
stuff. And you know what? I
gave you, I gave Eldo a good
recommendation. I take it back.
Eldo is not a good, he should
be unmodded. Take his wrench.
Eldo, what did you do? Eldo,
remember when you, Eldo, remember
when you shook your butt?
for me the other night on your show.
If he's going to talk shit about me, I'm going to put him.
He always fucking, oh, psyche this, psyche that, nagging,
coming back and forth.
Why psyche had LV on the panel?
Why psyche this?
But then he's over here fucking like trying
to be a rat about me.
I'm on your ass, fucking L though, idiot.
L though?
Yeah, he doesn't know what to say
because he's fucking talking shit.
L though.
Other remember when you shook your butt the other night on the show remember when he was like fucking spreading his ass for you to just fucking like
Bring psyche over here. Look at my fucking big ass. Everybody look at my fat ass. Yeah
Yeah, no shame take his wrench. I took it. He doesn't take my wrench away
I don't want to be a mod for you anymore like a fucking cry baby. Hey
Your wishes my command is taken. Oh dough. Are you there?
Hold on. I'm one or something. Okay. He's already something
It's okay
Penis pump thingy
The last one he's like order didn't work. It was too large for his penis. Oh my god. Yeah
It didn't fit right
I'm gonna drink I'm gonna have one more cigar. I don't know how long I said my pants are down. I'm in Speedos
I'm okay, so what would you say site?
I said, I'm in Speedos, Eldo.
I'm good for you, you know?
Congratulations.
Eldo, do you want to see?
Yeah.
No, I do not.
Eldo, that's for you.
Happy birthday, Eldo.
Say a pledge of allegiance, Eldo.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god
It's a nice thing I can do you smell that from here. My speedo smells good. It sounds good
If you went to Venice Beach like 15 years ago all the men at the mussel beach were wearing the same thing
It's not a big deal. Yeah
I'm so sorry
Like I said, you got to be careful with be because she she be talking shit about you
You know, I say it to his fucking face after all
You talk a lot of
Psychic what it's called is jealousy. She's jealousy
I'm gonna all the fucking like since that he collects like a G
She supports people that call others pedophiles. She supports
I'm just saying she supports JT
Okay, well, I'm just saying she supports JT post kids on this platform
You say elder are you making accusations you're being slanderous stop it elder. No, but it's true. It's true
I'm just saying it just happened like two days ago, and it was already taking care of so shut the fuck no
You you unmodded in them remodeled him
That's what I heard and then I took it away because he wanted to put a cat video in but he tricked me and he likes
I know so so not because he posts children but
All right, I have more standards than you you fucking doctor. Yeah, yeah, but it was cool if that's the case
It was cool with me, right?
No, I wasn't. I always told you I don't fuck
You pathetic you pathetic
Attack see me
No, I didn't yes, you did. I think Karen already cleared out 10,000 times
So you must be really fucking behind do your homework. I'm just no she she cleared it. She admitted to it
Yeah, she cleared it that I fucking you think Karen call someone I can call someone myself
You called Karen to attack semen for content
That is fucking absolute bullshit at the fucking lie and you're fucking lying. That's what she said
Actually said it wasn't true she knows I did and I wasn't even
Yeah, you're pathetic
I'm calling you out for being a bitch for being a pathetic drunk
And you're mad at me. Come on, man.
I think you're a pathetic fucking like no fucking life loser that nothing better to do than just come up.
Right. That's why I haven't I haven't been up here.
I haven't been up here while you've been doing while you've been doing lies while you've been doing lies.
I've been working getting money.
Right, yeah, yeah, your daddy pays for everything really I already fucking prove that to I should
For that
Fucking garage
I'm on the internet begging for money or fucking like giving money away to be a vest to be torn of a shoe.
You can't backstay.
You're pathetic. You have to pay to be a hoe.
You're mad. You're mad.
You said most of your money copying people.
You drink your life away. You drink your life away. That's all you do.
You're doing your money away for content supposedly. Hey, listen. Hey, I got money though
I mean my dad my dad don't got to give me the money though. My dad
Why do you think I money because I'm not
Look trying to get a kick me cry baby stop go drink a bottle
I don't drink vodka. Try again. Oh drink go drink a bottle of corona bitch. Go drink a bottle of corona. You drunk bitch.
I can do whatever the fuck I want. You have to be on the road. You start at the fucking you go to the lizard lot. You just look at the
$20 dirt bags and you look better than drink in my life away better than drink in my life away.
Well, I'll do whatever the fuck I want.
I bet you I love you though.
You're saying just saying
I eat better than you I fucking do more exercises than you know
I'm way better sheep than you are and you will be my
Know what you eat for dinner coronas, that's all you eat. No
That's why you look like a fucking toothpick because you fucking eat beer for fucking breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
You know, like a big gut? Like you?
I've proved I got a big gut. I saw your ass. It was just come on
You know what from now on I'm gonna call you beep beep because you when you back up it's probably like your wife is like beep beep
Be elder watch out. You're gonna like all the furniture. Just that's fine. Yeah. Yeah
I am at the perfect fucking way and I
I saw your butt, Eldo. You showed it. You shook it. I saw you shaking it on your show.
Eldo is gay for you and he wants to break up our friendship.
Okay, I'll go read there. I don't think you hear me. I'll go. I'm here
Okay, where you find it be the beat is
Psyche, you know
Friendship he's always
Part of EKG he wants to tattoo on his chest, right?
Psyche, you know how she really feel about you. She talks shit behind your back
She goes to your channel to complain about you. I'm not why I said it to his face. My issues with him what he did with Mr. Big Pies all of it
She tried to make me choose her over you psyche. No, I didn't I would never do that
She said listen
She says she said why are you supporting psyche? Why are you giving psyche money? You never said that?
You support them, but then you come over to my place and all you do is change pictures and try to get people
We were arguing about my question. Did you tell me did you say why do I support? Why do I support?
Yeah, you shady as hell
Why are we watching you here in Atlanta?
You don't want to make both other people and then you leave
and get put, you go somewhere else and you don't do the same thing
because you have to be vested, you have to pay like a bitch.
Hey listen, and it's probably too what Arthur said.
You probably do have sex with your uncle.
Wow
You probably do so you're gonna cry too about that. I'm not gonna cry to anybody. I'm just saying what you just said
Just really showed me. I don't ever want to fuck with you again. That's why that's the point. I'm making don't I'm not fucking with you
You come from the same kind of community that we know so it's good I would accept
You're gonna regret what you fucking said, you'll see. Oh, we'll see. Yep. You probably fuck your dad, too. There's old us
No, no, I can do it to beat it. No, don't don't talk
No, no, you're not gonna have to be like that. I'm gonna I'll beat you up
I'm gonna bend you over spank you. You're in trouble
Come on, you're supposed to choose guys over girls.
Did you just hear what he fucking said?
I hear it now, it's disgusting.
Hey, Elzo, now I'm supposed to, don't go that low.
My bad, I apologize to you, Psyche, I apologize.
No, no, no, no, no, don't say it.
Please, Elzo, stop it, stop it, like, please.
I'll make sure to go to Sandman's and say it.
Don't say it anywhere. That's horrible. It's horrible thing. I'll try it. Why are you being so mean?
No, because she's a fraud
No, no, no, I'm not saying nothing. She allows JT
To call Sam and a PDF, right?
You allowed yourself to talk to me like that. You're not really a man. It's okay. No, this is me being
Here with pure trash right now
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Oh, yeah, so now you now be that be then I was making up
And then you you said she was gonna say that psyche. She was already being fake to you psyche. No
So if I've proved to you that she was talking about you what you're gonna do
Forgive her. I don't care. She's anyone to talk about you talked about me. I heard you talking about me on others
No, no, no, no, no, no baddest. She talks about you because she jealous about you. She jealous
No, no, no, she's not be the beat is bigger than I am I'm just like a little fish. I'm a beat is a beat is a shark
I'm a little fish. Okay
No, no, no, don't talk to me like that. Okay. Oh, I'm just saying I did you know she got to get exposed to being a phone
No, no, no, do you want me to be fake?
No, why are you saying horrible thing that you're not supposed to say horrible things about people?
They look at the rules sitting out. They got the rules. I was are you breaking the rules? Is that respect for the panelists?
Psyche you tell her respect you there's it because it's beta
Because other people talk about other people up here when it's not be that you don't say nothing
You can say whatever she wants to say you
You're allowed you have to
You know what you're gonna do for beta. Huh? You're gonna unmind me for beta. Go ahead
You know that under the day. She's gonna she's gonna turn on you. No, she won't she will not. Oh my god
Hell God wants to God wants to God wants to talk to you know God wants to talk to you
What's up with all you weak ass fools up here always bitching about shit. What's going on with that?
Every day you up here bitching about some bullshit either you or some other clown
What's going on?
Yeah, I don't know this guy man. I'm good
You know
Now bitch answer the question. Why are you a bitch?
Somebody calls somebody pedophile and you bitching about every fucking day like a clown
What's this?
Y'all go to some bitch Academy, I don't know about
Some you guys cry every fucking day on a panel other way around you elder got me come on elder
You come to this dude's channel and you talk about bullshit
Oh, he called me a name. Oh, he called me a pedophile.
So fucking shut the fuck up.
Not just this clown, but every fucking clown.
You got nothing to talk about than saying
something dude called your fucking name?
OK, guys, let's go the fuck up.
Bunch of fucking pussies on here, man.
For real.
I know you're too nice to say that.
You're going to have to argue with somebody else
because you just got kicked out of the panel.
You just got kicked out of the panel.
Go ahead
Do it you got $25 do it make it 50, bitch
You must not know about me man. I don't know you're relevant. I know of people like you man. All you do is cry
You just a crying sucker, man, but you ain't gonna do nothing about it though
Although whatever the fuck
I'm sorry guys
Yeah, man, go ahead and kick me man cause I go ahead and go back to reading books
Nothing personal good. It's a very personal. Are you okay? I'll do I can't hear God. Is he here? Where you go?
No, God's been kicked for 24 hours. Oh, okay. He's gone. Okay. Come back to 24 man
6 p.m. 6 13, right?
Well guys, I do have the gong. Hold on. This is just ceremonial
Hit it hit it one time site doesn't make a noise
Yeah, and every time somebody get kicked, you know
But
That's how the cookie crumble sometimes guys it's not a cookie crumble. I'm just here while I'm just here watching but
Yeah, there's a cool gong it's a cool gong guys thinking did you like to for the gong that's a perfect idea
Elder you're mad at me. Are you mad at me elder?
No, I'm not mad. Okay, I'm mad at me
Okay, we're friends still or you're mad at me. No, no, why would I be what about me? What am I mad about?
I don't know. I don't know cuz I said you
Know where I stand so you good
Remember when you shook your butt on the on your show, but but you lying because you said I shook my butt for you
And I and that's all it was just dancing, but I saw that was there a guy that saw I did see it
I didn't see it. He was going like this. It was like this for
Like that, right, I'm glad you put me. Thank you for putting some pants on
No, I have Pamela
Thank you. You want to see the American flag?
I'm good, but but but the things like that I'm not understanding right now is you do you when you was just we was just talking about
I'll be there with state. We did we was are you sober or something like what was going on?
I'm not sober. I'm really drunk
Very drunk because you know how be to get you know, she was talking mad shit about you. So it's okay
BD can say whatever she wants I can say we are we all can I so we all gonna talk shit about each other. That's it
What what are you gonna say though? Don't say terrible things though. We were saying terrible things
You see nice say something nice
You want me to say something nice, that's a nice thing I could say be this face. No, no
Elzo you're white. Are you white or Puerto Rican?
Yeah, I'm caught. What do you have this isn't nice. It sounds like you're like Barry White or something. You have a such a nice voice
I love your voice
Hello
Okay, okay. Hey, Jamie's play the gong. Yeah
Guys, it's the gong show. This is how the second gong show you once guys
I'm just gonna take it to you and it's a nice touch it's a nice touch
Yeah, I know
Don't say horrible things
What's horrible? What did I say that was horrible?
Do you want do me here? Do you want to hear do me here? Do you sing a song? I'll sing a song to you
Go ahead. Yeah, go ahead and sing a song about how fake be the please do that for me
Come on do it for me
It's called suddenly see more be the be the only live the drink sing a song like that
We'll play play a beat for me and I'll rap a song about beta being
Lift up your head wash off your mascara here. Take my Kleenex wipe that lipstick away
Show me your face clean as the morning. I know things were bad, but now they're okay
Suddenly Seymour is standing beside you. You don't need no makeup
Don't have to pretend
Suddenly Seymour is here to provide you
Sweet understanding, Seymour's your friend, nobody ever treated me kindly.
Daddy left early, mama was poor.
I'd meet a man, I'd follow him blindly, he'd snap his fingers, I'd say, sure.
Suddenly Seymour is standing beside me, he don't give me orders, he don't condescend.
Suddenly, Seymour is here to provide me
Sweet understanding, Seymour's your
Tell me this feeling lasts till forever
Tell me the bad times are clean washed away
Please understand, it's still strange and frightening
For losers like I've been, it's so hard to say
suddenly see more suddenly see more he purified me he purified you suddenly
see more showed me I can't yes you can't suddenly see more the girl that's
inside me with sweet understanding see more is your friend that's it I'm sorry
Come on psyche. What was that? Come on man. It's this up of horse. Let us up of horse the best movie ever
So, so let me ask you this thank you
How do you how do you how did you feel when be the one that did do that?
Interview with Emma to find out why she disliked you. Oh, no, I would love I want to see that
I want to see the interview I want to see I want to see what Emma says
Well, because what I do to Emma I was her first member. I was one of her first mods
I was just supportive loving
Didn't interview I never was in it. I'd never I'd never use you. Yeah, I want to see I want to see it
It's okay. You see I want I want to be the interview be the you phony fake ass fuck beat beat is kitty gang
Fuck you. Oh, come on. I want to I'm talking about you. I'm talking about be the let me express my funds towards
But
I know because I never did anything bad. I think it was that I do one
I didn't do one negative thing if I did something I have something hateful towards that
She didn't hateful things towards me
Well, but you never do nothing to be there either and look what she did to you
No, be the beat be there. We are close friends. What was you what we gonna blame it on the alcohol?
Yes
I'm drunk. I'm drunk. I don't I don't you guys. Hey, Gish. How are you?
She beat even says she stopped talking to Karen, but this whole time she's been plotting against saying man, we care
You have called me names, um, all of this shit, and I said the same thing back to you and everything I say to you is to your face and you say it to me.
No, get the fuck out of here.
I'm not talking to you, bitch boy, okay?
Um, another thing, I have every right to be upset when I got upset at you over the Mr. Big Pipes thing.
No, you didn't!
A lot of people, you weren't there, you weren't there, shut up, nobody's talking to you.
You want to clap me, you can, it's 25 bucks, do it.
Big
You send joker money to gift learn diamonds only fans is that true or not?
Oh, we want to remember all of us were flirty diamond was to no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it was like
Cash shop or something like that and I said I'll send it to you
And then he paid for only fans and then he was supposed to pay me back
And then I was like I don't need it back like fucking keep it
But a flirty diamond can come up here and watch we were all on the panel
Wasn't working I don't know what it was but or if it was like PayPal or what he was like
I only have like cash up. I was like, okay, I'll send it to you. You can PayPal
I don't really remember but I was trying to help
she was introducing her only fans and i was like okay uh they were having money issue and i was
like that i wasn't exposing her that's fucking insane bita bita psych bita even told me that car
was was aggressive towards her you know what was aggressive towards her you're coming up with story
listen no you did you gave the money to joker my uncle fucks me and my dad fucks me so what kind
Hey look, you allowed JT, listen, you allowed JT to say that about saying that, okay?
You're mad, you're mad, you're mad.
I love your discord and I unmodded you, that's what you're mad about.
Did you, did you, did you, or did I ask you to unmod me?
No.
Who cares?
This is the internet.
The internet?
Don't call me on my back, anything like that.
I would never say that about your fucking family.
Just say it, I don't give a fuck.
Cry, baby. Go cry to somebody. Go cry to somebody. I'm not going to cry to nobody. You're going to be crying when something bad happens to you. It's called karma, bitch.
And then something will happen to your daddy gas station. Keep playing with me. Oh, my daddy has a gas station. What are you going to do? You're threatening my dad now?
Then you'll step my
Oh, so you're okay. So now you're threatening my fucking family. What you gonna do? You haven't called the police don't
I'm gonna tell you. I'm gonna do this. Psyche, come back. Psyche, come back.
Come back here. Come back.
Clap me is 25. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Nope. There's rules to the channel. It says no slander. No disrespect
Just because you paid to have gotty club doesn't mean that you can sit up here
Cry baby go cry go cry to Karen your new best friend
You're ghetto as fuck you're ghetto as fuck my friend or whoever is this the same friend as control us. Okay
I could be ghetto
We know we're not talking about big D. We're talking about true. Although you're the one that always said don't trust fucking Sam and don't trust very
You're fucking a shady person. Do you think I give a fuck if I ever said that yeah, I ever said that you think I give a fuck
Yeah, and you know what you're sitting up here, and you're fucking slandering my fucking family
And you're saying you're going after my stepmother who's like in her 70s. I spent on you bitch
And I'm a bit out of your stepmom. Oh, I cooked you cook me ho
Make sure you you got JC up there, bitch
Sam yeah, oh
What the fuck man, I had to drop the troop emergency call we drop we drop in and trooping God damn
I know what's just happened. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what's happening. What happened
We're drooping and trooping. I don't know what happened. I'd let people are what the fuck what happened
I'd like what the hell happened the shit was going crazy papas
Sam and do you see my speed oh Sam man?
No, I don't know. No, I don't want to see your fucking speedo
That's what made me like you make up last night.
He came on my panel, he's tripped and I was happy.
He made me laugh. I was so happy and me and psyche made up
So Eldo is mad because me and psyche made up and he's up here and he's like, oh
You should not mod beta da da da da da da da
And then he starts bringing up your situation going beta told Karen to go after salmon when it was cleared like 10,000 times
Be that allowed
Somebody to call like salmon's this and this and that I'm like well
I didn't allow anybody to call him that and they're not modded anymore da da da da and then you guys
You know what your uncle ever and your dad fucks you understand that? Yeah, what?
Yeah, and I like he did and I said, you know, I did I say I came back and then he started again
And then I said, um
Why is this coming out of the side? I think the the sky is coming out of the side
Sam, Sam, Sam, God bless America, Sam, and let's say God bless him, let's say, let's say,
pledge a pledge of allegiance, that's all you have to say. So then he goes like this, hold on,
let me just finish this because it's like one second, okay, then after he calls me those names,
I'm like, you know what, I wish the worst, I was like, you know, I believe in karma or something
like that, what goes, I like, I hope like whatever karma gets you, he goes, well, I'm going to go
to your dad's gas station and blow it up and I'm going to go after your stepmom, that's Aldo for you.
Yeah. How do you know what? What gas station? How the fuck? I don't know. But I mean like even
threatening it or telling him like telling me that my dad asked me now the fuck. Where's Elbow?
Elbow. Where'd you go? Elbow. Elbow. He's he ran away. Elbow.
Sammy you don't like the speedo though. You don't like it
The butt cheeks
No, let elbow talk what happened elbow
Stop doing that man you forced me to nah, bro stop site this sexual harassment site. I'm telling you I'm
watch your ass nigga it's clear it's clear it's completely it's it's so
good forcing people you're forcing it I'm not trying no no you know that's a
dog that's a dog no no no no no yeah you're forcing it yeah no no no you you
try what you kind of force your gay cheeks on me
Yeah, what's his name easy on camera?
What the fuck man come on bro, that's a gift from one of his fans easy but that's for him
It's a mace American flag guys. It's a little flag. I'll tell you what happened. Oh, go ahead
Here guys talk talk for a second. Oh damn your nails is dirty. What the fuck oh hell no you what you wipe your ass like that
I'm gonna go say oh my god
You
Yo, but what happened what I miss nigga go ahead and talk about it. No, I said what I had to say she keep trying let her cry
Only makes her look guilty. Let's remember that some man, you know when people say things that come out of their mouth
You can't control it on anyone's panel. This guy literally
All of that those are threats, okay any fucking just wandering on oh my dad gives me money
I don't care about any of that shit, but you're not gonna fucking threaten my family
I don't
Don't throw a family though
Nigga you use you said fucking KK kids with AIDS nigga shut your dumb ass up
You're okay. Oh, you literally my god asked me elder. That's like a far reach from like, you know things, you know
Why you keep saying that you may see what did you do it? You said it you said it
You want to forget about it, but I want you to know you said it. Okay 10 minutes ago. Okay. I'm supposed to feel bad
Yeah, you should actually you should be ashamed of your I know you should be you allowed you allow people to call same-man pdf
And he's supposed to be your boy. So shut your stupid
Anything back stage and keep and she
Fuck out of here. You think I called you that summer? I thought you was gonna lie. I didn't say I said you never call me that beta I
Thought you're gonna be all it's none of your fucking business what I'm gonna do right now
I'm gonna sit here if I want you can clap me if you like to although
You can't
When you provide the 25 for psyche
Knew I knew elbow is mad. I knew he was mad when he had to defend me. I knew he was that he was mad
That's elbow that's how I will
Y'all I can say the same thing about other crazy people
Everybody gets owns me for the 20th time bitch. That's so stupid. That's a go drink a bottle of corona
I'm not drunk. I don't have a drink.
You're fucking drunk.
She's not that level drunk.
She's not that level drunk, but she's drunk.
You drink every day, y'all.
You think you would know?
You do.
Yeah, you know me so well, right? You know me so fucking well
I won't even do that, bro, that's the sky rest in my case. Have a good day. What the fuck elbow. Hey, go cry, ho
Hey, they got that from my twin Arthur, nigga, you know what I mean?
Nah, you wildin', Elbow, what the fuck?
You dumb?
Nah, I won't even, you know I won't do that, so you wildin', nigga.
Ah, and we thought you wouldn't, we thought you would never talk about kids, but you said KK kids with AIDS, so, you know?
If you think that, you're salutes, man.
Oh, you know, you know, you never denied it nigga, you never
denied it nigga. Oh, oh, oh, you don't person that dies kids
and family. Listen, you never denied it. You never denied it.
Oh, oh, rely on you on the rage. I'm just here. I'm good. I'm
just here to listen to everybody. No, you stand on
that. So why are you getting mad?
I'm good
You don't stand on shit nigga talk about you gonna come be there you best friends with her again, nigga you phone
That's how slow you are now you probably forgot
Now elbow, I actually took the link on this morning
I took I was arguing with JT and then I came on site shit
It ain't no point nigga and what I'm not guaranteed be there was backstage and your stupid ass nigga
Giving her content nigga fuck that fucking drunk ass bitch. I got put backstage just well, you know shit happens
Then they she let me cook at the earth. She let me cook because I'm not
You was fucking thinking her for no reason
You was pathetic as her nigga
Well, listen, oh, but I had I thank you be the thank you be the I appreciate you be the thank you for letting me up be the
Giving her content nigga. You giving her content nigga
Yeah
Elbow elbow I had a cook would I had to cook
You ain't cook nothing they got
This morning what you cook nigga?
I next was crashing out
Listen, listen elbow. Why are you ranger? Let me explain to you. I next crashed out
She came she took the late and thought the trip kick video was new on it was a new live and I next called me a PDF
About my mama. I was like what the fuck she's the main crash out right there
Uh-huh
But I I next took the lake. It was crashing out. So I was
gonna crash out. She raised quit. Oh, I next was on a
crash out in JT. I mean, JT was on a crash out too. I try to
get the lives now. Let's play on the cancel. Eldo's lost his
mind. What's going on with Elger? When when Eldo's on the
rage, he's going to rain. And you kicked her. You kicked her.
If it be they don't got any respect for me as a as a you know, I'm saying
Right if you don't got respect for me, you think I'm gonna forget nah, bitch
You let the out I told you to chill you dumb bitch wing chill
like slow nigga like slow man see I don't forget you was mad I don't think
it's already telling me where where where you stay at and where your uncle
store at or your dad's store I keep fucking play with me ho yeah I'll give
a fuck y'all can clip it I don't give a fuck keep playing when you won't cook me
bitch I'm a roast you I'm a fucking deep-fried dumbass
One thing I give you that you you and I saw I said me you we cook different ways
But you know you be on that bullshit. Well, you stand on it. So I'll be on that bullshit. Thank you. I knew you was mad
I knew you was tight nigga
I cook nigga. I went to Alex panel all that nigga. You didn't see that I took Alex link that same night
I took Alex link. It was trying to make a big deal out of it. I
Said whatever whatever man, and I know okay, so no threat today guys guys guys
Don't don't mess with me on my channel. Don't mess with me on my channel. Okay. Don't mess with it. Okay. Don't mess with me
Like what you mean don't mess with beat us. Why you
I don't care. I don't care
She wants to say it be they can say I don't care. I don't care. She called
Elbow you about to lose this you about to lose sight too. Hmm. Yeah
I don't want to lose anybody. I love all you guys, but you're
You're just top donator
site remember
Damn boy, they're they try to push you out my nigga. Yeah, be the told him to unmod me and shit like be the
No more no more. No movie. Z. Be the told me to remind me
Rado you're so modest
But you're a thin I you're a thin ice and you keep messing with me because
Is it is my girl? No, but not that I might see a girl. She was just saying oh, come on man. You love her that much
Do come on man. She's gonna try to kiss your ass now nap them till you until you get rid of me
That's how fake she is
Why are you lying y'all though? Are you that that's right girl? I said no
Off the panel it doesn't mean that you can threaten them and say disgusting things about them
I don't fucking know and guess what psyche fucking calling me a bitch
I call them a bitch back. We called each other names. Um, you know, you like said he was evil
I'm a fool, you know, we heard each other and we're good. What you do good like what you can't like
on and get over it? Is that like so bad for you that you have to call me these kinds of names?
What is the bell though? Is it bothering you so much?
What's going on? What's going on right now?
I didn't ask him to unlock you. Stop fucking lying through your fucking ass. You lie.
He's gonna kiss your ass for a little bit, but he's just gonna lie. Okay. And you know what me and Samman are not gonna be like
Oh buddy, buddy
Cordial unlike you he would never
I wouldn't say that to him either never okay, you're sick yellow. It's not that deep either
Not that big stop crying
I love you guys
You know
You need elbows the evil God in the community elbows that you need the villain elbows literally playing the villain
I saw his butt. He has the evil butt. What?
Eldo, you remember when you shook your butt on the camera? I saw that
That wasn't for me, but it was on the camera. Yeah, niggas. Yeah niggas is fucking maggots, man. What the fuck is going on here?
psych what
Yeah, cool. That's a right up for a second. I'll be right back
Yo, you be doing coke man. You on the coke shit nigga. You stay disappearing for what?
Who oh, thank you. Yeah, he on the coke shit man
Maybe on a yo
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I told you. Look, look, he's back there. Oh, you got a little bit of white stuff on your, on your nose. Wait, wait, wait. I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't
I'm about to show you man.
Oh hell no, I'm not, ho ho ho, hell no.
Take it off, Sike.
I'm about to show you some salt, the most grave proof
and you still go forgive it.
That's why I'm probably going to take it a break, man.
I might be going for a couple of minutes.
It's okay, it's okay.
Whoa, whoa, what happened?
Oh hell no, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, what happened?
What are you showing?
Who's at Elisa's?
This is something you wanna see, Sike.
This something you wanna see, Sike.
I'm telling you, this something you wanna see, Sike.
Yeah, better than the Stambagapitas. You know, you know,
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude
Hello, he got to get a warm he got to get a warm
Yeah, like it's just momo for real
Rado, what are you cooking? What are you cooking a rado? You're cooking something?
This is the truth need to get out man
Sam it
Because it's not gonna show the way probably not gonna show the way with the way I'm doing it, but
Okay
Say this is how funny this bitch is I never had a DM where I'm talking shit about you man
This is no chat. This is how fake this girl is. I'm just letting y'all know chat
We read it read it psyche reader. I'm not I'm not impressed. Where you at read it
I can't deal with psych in his ways. He hurt me enough. He can go appreciate people like Emma and Elisa
Don't say anything, please. I know when to cut off shit off elder and they's always being
It's okay, it's okay
It's just discord stuff. It's just discord
Yeah, damn
Where be that be the you're coming to address it. Come on beta come address. I don't only think you are bitch
Why you taking your clothes off? No
Look sick you need to eat. Yeah, he tried to show his tattoo
Well, yeah, you look he can't hide the coat now. He want to do coke now. He want to do coke again
I'm telling you he on PCP nigga. Fuck you. He on PCP
He can't hide
Be this on the day and be the know where to be found be the gone now
She might have sparked up that love man
He ain't got no words for being a phony or maybe she went into discord man, but it's all good
I got everything you know, maybe she's the least you know
Be the fake man. That's not saying man. She's fake. That's I'm like, bro
You really kissing up the state and I knew say who's gonna forgive it. You know me
So it's like you got a brown stain in your undies, and I got niggas took a screenshot God
That is Photoshop guys. I spilled my coffee all over my speedo. Yeah, okay
You guys stage. Oh, no, there's no brown state. There's no brown
I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I can't believe it, I
And be the phony man at least at least if my father see you how phony this bitch is
Talking about he made up to me one day now. I'm not mad at now
I'm not gonna talk shit about psych and tell him how he picked guys over girls and this now
Cuz he fucking made you laugh be the such a stupid ass up bitch
Like I'm always keep it real bitch and you a phony asshole
Bitch keep crying man talking about he made me laugh man. That's just community
That's why if some people just low cows and some people just you know, not you know, I'm saying and be the
You definitely a low cow bitch
You better learn you were super low cow. We got regular. We got we got a regular low cause low cows
And we got super saying low cows, you know, I'm saying and beta, you know, what's your drunk?
She is super saying that guy
When be the drunk she is super saying you know like like motherfucking uh, what is that like Goku and all that nigga
I dragon balls, you know
Oh, let's make a shower come on man
You hear it
You said I hear it I
Told you it's the code
You think so come on
I ain't got enough money for that man. Is it the first of them? I mean it is early. He probably got a check
The way he acting so happy today, he might have got a check today, man. I
Think they give out food
Be the you fake bitch. I mean say man basically forgave you he forgave Kate. So I can't we can't even say that
How you say I forget
I would her well what you want to call okay now? I want to use my word right course. Okay. Well, she's gonna be cordial with you
You be cool about that?
That's it, but that's it, you still outlaw for them to call you a PDF though, man.
Like, you know, that's unforgivable, man.
He forgave payers right hammer, right twin.
Come on yo, he about to get cloud come on dog is you really doing this?
Look turn the camera
Phoenix why can't Phoenix in a Joker movie look
Like the name he looked like one of them feed you got a feed a kid
I'm only hearing right now. I'm going I'm going to ears. That's all I'm doing. I'm boy. I got that air
No soap nigga wash that nigga wear a soap at nigga this nigga washing up like Ian Rikers nigga. What a soap
Come on
Get your boy
Get your boy. Who boy? This isn't chat man. Who can I say get your boy, man?
Where you at Jamie to get your boy, Jamie?
Get your boy, Jamie
They got no soap my nigga, I swear to God this nigga got no soap. Oh
Nick in the child look Jim Nick in there. Is that real? Yeah, that's Jim Nick. Jim Nick come up here
We got to talk to you man
Hey, Jimmy, you can't touch the phone. He got how you go
Terrifying so this thing is fucking gay my nigga. You're doing too much site. So I hate y'all now you do
I hate you nigga. No, no, no, I'm lit. No, I hate you nigga
I don't spank this yo, I don't smack this shit out of you. I'll go drag you
Nah, you're wallowing now. You're doing too much site
How about this is this is a gas to us man trying to care
Send the camera off TOS. No, you don't even watch it. There was no soap. They can watch it. That's what no soap
You still watching you homeless nigga, man over here watching I took the screen off nigga
Come on
You want some more?
Let Jimmy up
Jimmy yeah, Jim Nick. Oh
Jim Nick backstage. She not back. Oh, yeah, I'm out of here. I can't take this nigga. He's wallet. No, I can't take this
Is he backstage?
Yo, who backstage site?
Move backstage. Nobody I
Don't even think this motherfucker here
Where the shampoo where the shampoo they saying you ain't even using shampoo where the shampoo
Damn, he ain't even using sand poo poo
Beta you fake you phony beta you phony beta
You fake beta you phony hoe
Let's see if I got a beta picture
They'll be a little busy going that all soon.
Anyhow.
Nope.
I think I did.
Let me see, let me see.
Oh my thought I had been
No, no
Why am I that way, babe?
Gemney!
Hold on, give me one sec, I've always forgotten to do shit
The face is puppy
I don't like your speedo.
Go USA.
Oh.
I had to come up to make it a little less gay,
so y'all aren't just the three guys hanging out.
Oh my goodness.
Hey Aldo, would you, would you do?
Thank you.
Take a gay tail man. What up, Jim knit you're probably not gonna like me after the day, but either I mean it's all good
So you don't care if I went at your girl cool cool
Why'd y'all go at it
Because of what happened on her live a couple of days ago man. She was doing some weird ass shit. You get the drinking and do dumb shit
I wasn't watching
This ain't my war Jim except for she ain't choosing beta or me beta beta you listen to beta
Jim Nick team L don't know the context of the situation
Help what am I to judge if I don't know what's going on
Who's there?
Whoa!
Warbomb!
Let's go!